<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE tmx SYSTEM "tmx11.dtd">
<tmx version="1.1">
  <header creationtool="OmegaT" o-tmf="OmegaT TMX" adminlang="EN-US" datatype="plaintext" creationtoolversion="5.1.0_0_54fc30ee9" segtype="paragraph" srclang="zh-CN"/>
  <body>
<!-- Default translations -->
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>###第一章 重生成为团宠</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T151633Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T151633Z">
        <seg>Chapter 1: Reborn As The Apple Of Everyone's Eyes </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>###第七章 一个谁也惹不起的方式</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T152319Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T152319Z">
        <seg>Chapter 7: A Method That No One Can Provoke </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>###第三章 同意订婚一事</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T125733Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T125733Z">
        <seg>Chapter 3: Agree To The Engagement</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>###第九章 这么听话</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T134050Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T134050Z">
        <seg>Chapter 9: So Obedient </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>###第二章 订婚一事</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T165426Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T165426Z">
        <seg>Chapter 2: The Engagement </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>###第五章 给他发照片</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T161025Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T161025Z">
        <seg>Chapter 5: Send Him A Photo </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>###第八章 她碰瓷？</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201210T133246Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201210T133246Z">
        <seg>Chapter 8: She's Scamming? </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>###第六章 男人的夸赞</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T173753Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T173753Z">
        <seg>Chapter 6: A Compliment From Him</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>###第十一章 我也不能白受了这个委屈不是</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T171308Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T171308Z">
        <seg>Chapter 11: I Can't Be Wronged For Nothing, Can I?</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>###第十三章 罚站</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201215T152944Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201215T152944Z">
        <seg>Chapter 13: Punished To Stand </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>###第十二章 徐晗</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T182646Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T182646Z">
        <seg>Chapter 12: Xu Han</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>###第十章 倒戈</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T163815Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T163815Z">
        <seg>Chapter 10: Reversal </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>###第四章 想他</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T143640Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T143640Z">
        <seg>Chapter 4: Miss Him </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>2020年？</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T162316Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T162316Z">
        <seg>Year 2020!?!  </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“不是吧？我不是听说她被人包养了吗，还要嫁给那个公司的老总来着，听说那个人对她可大方了，她用的首饰，都是天价呢！”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T133201Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T133201Z">
        <seg>"Seriously? I heard she became someone's mistress and that she's going to marry a CEO of a company. I heard that that person is very generous to her. All of her accessories are exorbitant!" </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“不然咱们发上贴吧问问，贴吧这么大，总有人认识吧？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T131055Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T130920Z">
        <seg>"Why don't we put it up on Baidu Tieba [1. Baidu Tieba is a Chinese communication and forums platform, hosted by Chinese search engine company Baidu.] and ask around? There must be someone who knows who she is, right?"</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“不知道具体情况还这么说，让大家误会，难怪叶漓这么生气，要是我妹妹这样说，我也会生气的。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T165246Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T165246Z">
        <seg>"She doesn't know the details and yet she still said that to cause a misunderstanding for everyone. No wonder Ye Li is so angry with her, I'd be infuriated if my sister said so too."</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“不过这样也好，他们都是咱们向阳粉，哪有一家人自相矛盾呢，都是姐妹啊不是吗？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T180433Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T180433Z">
        <seg>"However, this is good, they are both fans of Xiangyang. How can there be conflicts within the fan club? We're all sisters, aren't we?"</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“也怪那个叶眉，什么都不知道就乱说话，不知道自己什么身份嘛，不然也不会害的咱们自家人差点反目成仇啊！”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T180651Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T180635Z">
        <seg>"It's all Ye Mei's fault. If she doesn't know anything, she should just keep quiet. She caused us fans of the same club to almost fall out with each other!" </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“二弟，让人去查查，我倒是想看看那个不想活了的，竟然敢嚼我妹妹的舌根！”叶洛阴沉的道。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T181952Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T181952Z">
        <seg>"Second Brother, go get someone to investigate on this matter. I want to see who has the audacity to do this to my sister!" Ye Luo said sullenly. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“什么鬼？她坐那里？那不是那个叶漓的位置吗？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T183807Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T183807Z">
        <seg>"What the hell? She's sitting there? Isn't that Ye Li's seat?"</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“什么！他说你恶心！”三人的脸一下就阴沉了下去。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T140205Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T140205Z">
        <seg>"What!?! He said that you're disgusting!?!" The faces of her three brothers grew sullen. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“你为我着想？你为我着想所以就把我推了出来承受一切责任，然后被万夫所指是吗？我为什么要背上这莫须有的罪名，你作为我的妹妹不帮我说话就算了，还向大家实证就是我的错，当真是我的好妹妹啊，要不是当时你没在现场，我都要以为你是亲眼所见了！”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T150037Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T150037Z">
        <seg>"You're sparing a thought for me? Just because you spare a thought for me, you can push me out to bear all the responsibility and then make me bear the responsibility for something that I didn't do? You're my younger sister but you didn't stand up for me. You even made it clear to everyone that it's my fault. You're really my wonderful sister. If not for the fact that you weren't there when it happened, I would have  thought that you saw it with your own eyes!"</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“你们不要这样说，我姐姐遇到这样的事情，她已经十分伤心了，我希望大家能看在我的份儿上，不要再纠结这件事了。”听到同学们的猜测，叶眉有些生气的停下脚步，维护叶漓道。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T133545Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T133545Z">
        <seg>"Don't say that, my sister is already extremely upset because of this matter. I hope that you can all stop harping on this matter for my sake." Upon hearing the conjectures of her schoolmates, Ye Mei stopped in her tracks angrily and defended Ye Li. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“你们有没有发现，她好像就是叶漓？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T183819Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T183819Z">
        <seg>"Have you guys not noticed that she seems to be Ye Li?"</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“你们没听说吗？她前段时间去找于向阳表白，结果当场被拒，跳河自杀了，当时来了好多警察，我还以为救不回来了，啧啧。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T133022Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T133022Z">
        <seg>"Haven't you guys heard? She confessed to Yu Xiangyang previously but ended up getting rejected by him. She decided to jump into the river to kill herself. At that time, there were many police officers and I thought that she'd definitely die. Tsk, tsk." </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“你怕是巴之不得才对吧。”叶漓心中暗嘲。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T141816Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T141816Z">
        <seg>'You'd probably be more than happy if that happens.' Ye Li sneered and thought to herself.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“你没听她姐姐说了吗？她当时也不在现场，并不知道具体情况。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T165151Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T165151Z">
        <seg>"Didn't you hear what Ye Li said? Ye Mei wasn't there at the time and she doesn't know the details of what happened." </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“你胡说八道，我们是粉丝，就有义务维护偶像的名誉，而且这件事本来就是你的错，凭什么要我们偶像承担责任！”女生怒目而视。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T141424Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T141424Z">
        <seg>"Bullshit. Since we're his fans, it's our duty to defend our idol's reputation. Besides, you're the one at fault in this matter. Why does our idol have to take responsibility!?!" the girl retorted as she glowered at Ye Li. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“做了就做了，她妹妹都说了，她还死不承认，估摸着真的是想碰瓷学长吧。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T145603Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T145603Z">
        <seg>"Her sister has already said that she had done it. Yet, she still refuses to admit it. I bet she's really trying to scam Senior." </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“先说这些话的都是我们班上的同学，我也不知道她们从何得知。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T181504Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T181504Z">
        <seg>"The ones who started saying these were my classmates. I don't know how they found out either." </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“只有我的注意力在她脸上吗？你们看她的眼睛，好漂亮哎，标准的狐狸眼，我去，还有泪痣，这么勾人的眼睛，以前我怎么就没发现呢？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T132616Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T132616Z">
        <seg>"Am I the only one who's paying attention to her face? Look at her eyes, they're beautiful. She has a perfect pair of fox eyes and a damned mole under the corner of her eye. They're so mesmerizing. Why haven't I noticed them before?"</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“可不是嘛....”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T133242Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T133242Z">
        <seg>"Exactly..." </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“可不是嘛....”众人厌恶的道。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T145659Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T145659Z">
        <seg>"Exactly..." Everyone agreed with disgust towards Ye Li. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“可不是嘛，以前还觉得她情商挺高会说话，现在看来，也不怎么样嘛。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T180725Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T180725Z">
        <seg>"Exactly. I used to think that she had a high EQ and was very tactful with her words but it seems that she isn't that good after all." </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“可以啊。”叶漓大方的掏出了手机，两人互相交换了联系方式，在众人风中凌乱的表情中，女同学兴奋的离开了。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T175956Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T175956Z">
        <seg>"Sure." Ye Li graciously took out her mobile phone and the two of them exchanged contacts. While everyone was looking on in shock, the girls left excitedly. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“同学，你别这样，哎呀，姐姐，你快跟人家道歉呀？”叶眉一脸着急担忧的看向叶漓，那模样好似是真的很关心。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T142654Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T142654Z">
        <seg>"Please don't be like this, schoolmate. Ah, Sister, hurry and apologize to her," Ye Mei said, looking at Ye Li worriedly, as if she was truly concerned. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“呵~”叶漓闻言，嗤笑了一声：“你作为我的妹妹，竟然不相信我，反倒是和外人合伙来逼我道歉，承担所有的责任，这知道的，以为你是在关心我，不知道的，恐还以为你和她们是一伙的，我就奇怪了，你也没亲眼看见啊，怎么就笃定了这事是我的错呢？你不是一向最关心我，一直站在我的身边的吗？怎么这会儿，却帮着外人来陷害我？”她疑惑又怀疑的看向叶眉，“还是说，人家给你钱了，你这么帮她？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T143654Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T143612Z">
        <seg>Upon hearing her words, Ye Li sneered, "Ah, you're my younger sister and yet, you don't believe me at all.Instead, you gang up with others to force me to apologize and take full responsibility. Those who know what happened will think that you're showing me concern but those who don't might just think that you're in cahoots with them. I find it really strange. You did not see that happen with your own eyes, how are you so sure that it's my fault? Haven't you always been the most concerned about me? Haven't you always stood on my side? Why are you now ganging up with others to frame me?" Looking at Ye Mei apprehensively in confusion, she asked, "Or are you helping her because she paid you?" </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“呵，这就把你吓到了？”叶漓上前，拍了拍女同学僵硬的肩膀，笑的和善极了：“我吓吓你而已，都是一个学校的同学，我怎么也不会做的这么过分，我也明白做粉丝的想维护偶像的心情，我也是学长的粉丝，怎么能不懂你的感觉呢，只是我们同为他的粉丝，何必自相残杀，我知道，可能刚刚是因为我妹妹的话，才会让你误以为真，发生了这样的事，我能理解。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T175341Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T173053Z">
        <seg>"Hah, did that frighten you already?" Ye Li stepped forward to smack the stiffened shoulders of the girl. Smiling kindly, she said, "I was just scaring you. We're still schoolmates from the same school, I won't go so overboard. I understand that you're just a fan who wants to defend your idol. As a fan of Senior, how can I not understand how you feel? However, since we're both fans of the same idol, we shouldn't turn against each other. I know that you only got mistaken because of my sister's words."</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“咦？她身后那个女生是谁啊？”看到叶眉身后又走下一个穿着校服的女孩，她扎着高马尾，朝气蓬勃，脸看起来十分圆润，在一双星眸的映衬之下，十分可爱，她素颜朝天，可肤若凝脂，白里透红，像极了垂涎欲滴的红苹果，原本精心打扮的叶眉，相比对之下，突然给人的感觉就能没那么自然了。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T122859Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T122345Z">
        <seg>"Huh? Who's that girl behind her?" They saw another girl behind Ye Mei who was wearing a school uniform and had her hair up in a high ponytail, which was voluminous and stylish. Her face was round and she looked extremely adorable without makeup. Her skin was fair and slightly rosy, like delicious apples. In comparison, Ye Mei, who had exquisitely dolled herself up, seemed rather unnatural.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“咱们学校什么时候有这么纯天然的女孩了，为什么我都不知道？”其他人也纷纷朝着叶漓投去惊讶的目光。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T124459Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T124459Z">
        <seg>"Since when have we ever had such a pure and natural schoolmate?" Everyone else was looking at Ye Li in shock. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“哥哥，我不怪你，要怪就怪我瞎了眼吧，不过没关系，我已经看清楚了他的真面目了，我以后再也不会喜欢他。”叶漓摇了摇头，看着三哥自责，她也无比心疼。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T141350Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T141350Z">
        <seg>"Brother, I don't blame you. I can only blame myself for being blind, but it doesn't matter, I've already seen his true colors clearly. I won't fancy him anymore from now on." Ye Li shook her head, looking at her Third Brother who was ridden with remorse, feeling extremely heartbroken. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“哦？一个八竿子打不着一点关系的粉丝？你有什么资格？你们偶像知道你背地里这样自作主张了吗？”叶漓嗤笑一声，看她的眼神仿佛在看一个笑话：“还是说，于向阳本人不敢站出来说话，需要你这个小小的粉丝来找我为他洗白开脱？啧，这么听话吗？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T140320Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T140320Z">
        <seg>"Oh? A fan who's completely unrelated to him? What right do you have? Does your idol know that you're acting presumptuously like this behind  his back?" Ye Li sneered, as if she was looking at a joke. "Or is it that Yu Xiangyang is too timid to stand up for himself so he needs a fan like you to confront me and clear his name? Tsk, are you that obedient?"</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“哦？所以你也承认这不过就是谣言，而你仅仅因为听别人道听途说，就来找我麻烦了？”叶漓邪气一笑：“警察叔叔抓人都还要证据呢，你这证据都拿不出来，就开始逼我道歉，还放话威胁，这应该已经构成犯罪了吧，咱们要不要去警察叔叔那里谈谈，看看这件事如何解决，毕竟....”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T171805Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T171805Z">
        <seg>"Oh? So you admit that it's just a rumor too and that you've come to make trouble for me just because of something you found out based on hearsay?" Ye Li laughed sinisterly and continued, "Even the police needs evidence to arrest someone. You started forcing me to apologize without having any evidence. That alone should have constituted a crime, right? Why don't we settle this at the police station? After all..." </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“哦？那好吧。”这次叶漓没有生气，反倒是笑着附和了一声。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T141939Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T141939Z">
        <seg>"Oh? Okay then." Ye Li was not enraged this time. Instead, she smiled and agreed. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“喂？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T145019Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T145019Z">
        <seg>"Hello?" </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“大哥二哥三哥，你们不用担心，我没事。”叶漓瓮声瓮气的道。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T164759Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T164723Z">
        <seg>"Big Brother, Second Brother, Third Brother, don't worry, I'm alright," Ye Li said in a hoarse voice. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“大哥二哥三哥，我知道了，我不会再这样了，这一次要不是因为同学们嘲笑我，我也不会想不开...”叶漓低着头擦了擦眼角的湿润，伤心的说。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T174511Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T174511Z">
        <seg>"Big Brother, Second Brother, Third Brother, I know, I won't do this again. If my classmates hadn't mocked me this time, I wouldn't have let my emotions rule over my head..." Ye Li said miserably as she hung her head low and rubbed the tears at the corner of her eyes.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“大小姐和叶眉小姐关系那么好，你当然不会欺负她的。”司机肯定的说。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T155655Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T155655Z">
        <seg>"Missy and Miss Ye Mei are on such good terms with each other. Missy, of course you wouldn't bully her," the chauffeur said firmly. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“好可爱啊，你看她那双眼睛，也太漂亮了吧，我隔这么远都能看到浓密的睫毛，自带眼线哎，还有一颗泪痣，妈耶，微胖中的极品！”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T123331Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T123101Z">
        <seg>"She's so adorable. Look at her eyes, they're so beautiful. I can see her luscious and voluminous eyelashes. She has natural eyeliner and a mole under the corner of her eye. Oh my, she's a gem among chubby girls!"</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“妈，我姐不会有事吧？”叶眉担忧的问道。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T145811Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T145811Z">
        <seg>"Mother, my sister will be fine, right?" Ye Mei asked worriedly. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“姐姐怎么样了，还好吗？她是不是又闹了，我跟她关系最好，要不要我去劝劝她？”叶眉又关心的问。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T151215Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T151136Z">
        <seg>"How is Sister? Is she alright?  Is she making a scene and throwing a tantrum again? I'm the closes to her. Should I go and talk some sense into her?" Ye Mei asked with concern. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“害，我确实不懂。”司机大叔憨憨的抓了抓头发，“不过大小姐这样看起来真的好看。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T153454Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T153454Z">
        <seg>"I really don't," the chauffeur said, scratching his head foolishly. He continued, "But Missy really looks good now." </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“对啊，我差点就以为是真的了，只是好奇怪，为什么叶眉学妹一直那样说呢，害的我以为真有女的这么傻，表白被拒就自杀的，太狗血了有木有。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T165130Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T165130Z">
        <seg>"Yeah, I almost thought it was true. I was just confused about why Junior Ye Mei kept saying that. She made me think that there are really such foolish girls who would attempt suicide because they had been rejected after confessing. That's too cliché."</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“对啊，而且咱们班级，就她最胖，没错了。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T184155Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T184155Z">
        <seg>"Yeah, besides, she's the chubbiest girl in class. It must be her." </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“对对对，赶紧发问问到底是谁。”几人匆忙转身离开，连其他人也没心思再拍了。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T131136Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T131136Z">
        <seg>"Yeah, hurry and ask around, find out who she is." The few of them frantically turned around to leave. Even the rest were no longer in the mood to continue taking photos. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“导师好。”叶眉乖巧的打了一声招呼，刚刚难看的脸色已经消失不见，如今的她看起来格外的乖巧。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T182141Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T182113Z">
        <seg>"Hello, Teacher," Ye Mei greeted obediently. The look of displeasure on her face had long disappeared and she now looked extremely well-behaved. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“小妹，以后万不可再做这样的傻事了知道吗？哥哥们知道你喜欢于向阳，以后再也不会逼你嫁给徐凤年了。”另一个长相十分斯文，看起来书生气息颇浓的男人无奈又心疼的劝道。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T160455Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T160455Z">
        <seg>"Little sister, don't ever do such a foolish thing, alright? We, your brothers, know that you fancy Yu Xiangyang and we'll never force you to marry Xu Fengnian again," said another scholarly-looking man who seemed mild-mannered. He felt helpless and took pity on his younger sister. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“就她这样的，竟然还有脸惦记咱们的男神，也不撒泼尿照照自己。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T133237Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T133237Z">
        <seg>"With that face of hers, she actually has the cheek to harbor designs on our idol. Why don't she take a look at herself in the mirror?"</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“就是，男神的身份本就敏感，要是这事被传出去，大家肯定会说是他逼得叶漓自杀，那咱们男神的前途可不就毁了吗？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T134440Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T134440Z">
        <seg>"Exactly, our idol's identity is sensitive in the first place. If this gets out, people will definitely say that he forced Ye Li to commit suicide. His future will then be ruined!" </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“徐晗哎，他终于来学校了！”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T185139Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T185139Z">
        <seg>"It's Xu Han, he's finally in school!"</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“怎么了，生气了？虽然你换了个发型，但是这也改变不了你就是个小胖妞的事实啊。”反应过来的他欠揍的道。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T191600Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T191600Z">
        <seg>"What's the matter? Are you upset? You may have had a change of hairstyle but that does not change the fact that you are a little fatty," he said in an annoying manner after reacting from the shock. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“怎么了？你要是受不了这个委屈，我也不介意去帮你讨个公道？”叶漓直接了当的笑。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T142101Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T142101Z">
        <seg>"What's the matter? If you can't take it lying down, I won't mind standing up for you and doing you some justice." Ye Li laughed straightforwardly. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“怎么可能，那个小肥妞哪有这么好看？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T183844Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T183844Z">
        <seg>"How is that possible? How can that little fat girl be so good-looking?"</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“怎么天天都是这些东西？”她不悦的往后一靠，没有看向看过来的秦柔母女，反而是看向了一旁站着的女佣。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T143849Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T143849Z">
        <seg>"Why do I get served these stuff everyday?" She leaned backwards in displeasure and stared at the maid at the side instead of Qin Rou and Ye Mei. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“怎么没听老师说过会有新同学，白白胖胖的长得好可爱呀。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T183115Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T183115Z">
        <seg>"Why didn't Teacher inform us that we'd be having a new classmate? She's fair and chubby, so adorable."</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“怎么，这位同学好似还有些不甘心呢，还想要我去承担这个罪名吗？”叶漓抬了抬下巴，轻蔑的看向脸色难看的女生。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T170747Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T170747Z">
        <seg>"Why? You still seem to be a bit indignant. Do you still me to take the blame?" Ye Li lifted her chin and looked at the girl whose face had grown sullen, with contempt. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“我不怪你们，我知道你们是为了我好才会让我同徐大少订婚，而且这是妈妈的心愿，我也想要帮她实现。”叶漓下定决心道。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T134425Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T134425Z">
        <seg>"I don't blame you guys. I know you wanted me to marry Young Master Xu for my own good. Besides, it's also Mother's wish. I want to fulfill it for her," Ye Li said after making up her mind. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“我为什么要道歉？”叶漓歪着头，疑惑的看向她问。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T142927Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T142927Z">
        <seg>"Why should I apologize?" Ye Li questioned, staring at her with confusion as she tilted her head. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“我也不知道，我要和老...徐大少订婚的消息不知道被谁传播了出去，同学们都在说，我要嫁给那些年纪大的老男人做老婆，还说我之前那么有钱，就是被人包养，明明都不是这样的，可大家都这样说，这让我日后要怎么见人？”叶漓一句老公差点脱口而出。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T175037Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T175037Z">
        <seg>"I don't know, the news of my engagement with Hub... I mean, Young Master Xu, was somehow spread by someone. My classmates all said that I'm marrying an old man and that I must be able to live a luxurious life because I'm the mistress of a wealthy man. That's obviously not the truth but now that they're saying such things, how am I going to face anyone in the future?" Ye Li almost blurted the word 'Hubby'.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“我也是，不过这女的到底谁啊，我们学校有这样的人我竟然不知道？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T130853Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T130853Z">
        <seg>"Me too, but who is this girl? How come I don't know that there's someone like her in school?"</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“我也觉得，人家也说了只是粉丝，现在的粉丝追星疯狂也能理解，但是去为了他死，好像是太过夸张了吧。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T165023Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T165023Z">
        <seg>"I think so too. She's already said that she was just a fan and it's understandable that fans nowadays would rave over their favorite celebrities hysterically but dying for him seems a bit too exaggerated." </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“我怎么看，觉得她好像是叶漓啊？就叶眉那个姐姐，你们看像不像？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T131837Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T131837Z">
        <seg>"She looks like Ye Li to me. Ye Mei's sister, Ye Li. Don't you guys think so?"</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“我是你的姐姐，刚刚也没见你相信我？”叶漓直接原话返回，表情嘲讽，所以说你有什么资格让我相信？</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T170229Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T170229Z">
        <seg>"I'm your older sister but you didn't believe me just now either." Ye Li immediately retorted her with the same words and a look of mockery. 'So, what right do you have to make me believe you?' She thought. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“我是死了吗？不然为什么会见到哥哥他们？”她瞪着美目，不可置信的喃喃。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T154329Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T154329Z">
        <seg>"Am I dead? Otherwise, how can I see my brothers?" Her beautiful eyes were wide open and she was muttering in disbelief. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“我的错？你亲眼看到我跟他表白了，你又亲眼看到我为了他自杀了？你什么都不知道，就来让我去澄清道歉？凭什么？凭你那张会说话的嘴？”叶漓不屑的目光落到了对方难看的脸上。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T141559Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T141559Z">
        <seg>"I'm at fault? Did you people see me confessing to him and killing myself because of him? You people want me to clarify matters and apologize to him when you don't know anything at all? Why should I do that? Because you're good at talking?" Ye Li looked at the girl with disdain. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“我相信这学校有一半的女生都喜欢向阳学长，向他表白的人数不胜数，我不过就是刚好出了一点意外而已，怎么落到你们口中，就变成了碰瓷报复了呢？想象力这么丰富，你们还需要读什么书啊，去报刊写小说好了。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T164519Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T164519Z">
        <seg>"I believe half of the girls in school adore Senior Xiangyang and have confessed to him before. However, I only happened to fall into the water by accident. Why did you people turn it into a scam and a plot for revenge? Since you've got such a rich imagination, why bother studying? You guys should just join the newspaper agencies and write novels for them."</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“我知道改变不了什么，所以有事？”想到此，叶漓冷淡的回应了一句。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T191730Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T191730Z">
        <seg>"I know it won't change anything, so what's the matter?" Ye Li answered calmly at the thought of this. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“我觉得之前的还是要好看一些，还能遮住你的缺点。”她有意无意的强调。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T152711Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T152600Z">
        <seg>"I still think that your previous hairstyle looks better. At least, it can hide your flaws," she deliberately emphasized in a passive-aggressive manner. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“我都说了，咱们是同学，一句对不起就能解决的事情，何必闹大，你说呢？”叶漓一笑，可笑容不达眼底。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T175420Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T175420Z">
        <seg>"I said, we are classmates. Why bother blowing up something that can be resolved with an apology?" Ye Li said with a smile, but it was not genuine. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“我，我没有，姐姐，你别误会，我真没有其他意思。”她赶忙解释。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T164029Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T164029Z">
        <seg>"I-I didn't, Sister, don't get the wrong idea, I really didn't mean anything else," she hurriedly explained.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“换做是我告白被拒绝，还被人逼着道歉的话，我可能也会气死的吧。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T171000Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T171000Z">
        <seg>"If I were the one who got rejected after confessing and was even forced to apologize, I'd probably hit the roof." </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“是吗？”叶漓啧了一声：“那我倒是想看看，你们要怎么不放过我了。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T142104Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T142104Z">
        <seg>"Is that so?" Ye Li clucked her tongue against the roof of her mouth and said, "I shall see how you deal with me then."</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“是吗？”她若有所思的看了叶眉一眼。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T140840Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T140840Z">
        <seg>"Is that so?" she asked, looking at Ye Mei, seemingly filled with thoughts. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“是啊....”众女生原本看叶漓愤怒的目光，逐渐变成了好想结交的期待眼神。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T180521Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T180521Z">
        <seg>"Yeah..." The angry gazes of the girls who were looking at Ye Li with displeasure, gradually turned into looks of anticipation as they were eager to befriend her. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“是啊阿漓宝贝，你吓死哥哥了，你要是出了一点事，要哥哥们日后怎么办呀。”蓝发男同样是一脸伤心。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T160605Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T160553Z">
        <seg>"Yeah, Baby Li, you scared us. If anything happens to you, what are we supposed to do in the future?" the man with the blue hair said, looking just as sad as the others. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“是啊阿漓，你不是喜欢向阳吗？你要是喜欢，哥哥怎么也得帮你拿下他，我们也不想你不幸福。”叶枫也是认同道。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T134921Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T134736Z">
        <seg>"Yeah, Li, don't you like Xiangyang? If you fancy him, I must help you win his heart no matter what. We want you to be happy too," Ye Feng chimed in.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“是啊，你们不说我还忘记这号人了，平时叶漓也跟叶眉来学校，但是跟在后面，压根没什么存在感，我从没有关注过，有些印象，这个女的看起来跟她一样胖，就是贞子发型没了，差别好大啊，我完全没认出来。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T132507Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T132507Z">
        <seg>"Yeah, if you guys didn't mention her, I would have forgotten about her. Usually, Ye Li would follow behind Ye Li and she barely has any presence at all. I've never paid attention to her and I only have a vague impression of her. This girl looks chubby, just like her, but she no longer has a Sadako hairstyle. The difference is huge. I really didn't recognize her at all." </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“是啊，叶眉都这样维护她了，还被她指责，真是太不值了。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T145637Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T145637Z">
        <seg>"Yeah, Ye Mei is already defending her. Yet, she still chided Ye Mei. It really isn't worth Ye Mei's while."</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“是啊，还威胁说向阳粉不会放过她的呢，现在的粉丝都这么嚣张的吗？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T170837Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T170837Z">
        <seg>"Yeah, she even threatened her by saying that Xiangyang's fans wouldn't let her off. Are fans all so arrogant nowadays?" </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“是啊，长得挺漂亮的啊，之前怎么就打扮成那副模样，真是奇怪，不过这会儿突然换了新发型，难不成是开窍了？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T132728Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T132728Z">
        <seg>"Yeah, she's quite pretty. Why did she use to make herself look that way? That's so strange. However, she suddenly changed her hairstyle. Has she woken up her idea?"</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“是，他是说我恶心，说我仗着自己跟三哥哥的关系就纠缠他！”叶漓眼泪汪汪的告状。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T140528Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T140528Z">
        <seg>"Yeah, he said that I'm disgusting and that I keep pestering just because I'm Third Brother's younger sister!" Ye Li complained with tears in her eyes. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“没事就好，昨晚上我就想去看你了，但是哥哥他们不让，我才没有去看你。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T173726Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T173726Z">
        <seg>"Good that you are. I wanted to go see you last night but Brothers didn't allow me to so I didn't." </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“没事，我不怪你，毕竟我也知道，你和向阳学长来往关系那么密切，帮着他的忙说我我也能理解，我确实因为表白被拒而伤心，但是我不觉得那足够让我想不开自杀，落水本就是一个意外，到了妹妹的口中却变成了自杀，好像是生怕别人不知道我为情自杀似的，啧，我这还真是跳进黄河也洗不清了。”叶漓无奈耸肩。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T164219Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T164219Z">
        <seg>"It's alright, I don't blame you. After all, I know that you've always been close to Xiangyang and I can understand why you want to help him. Indeed, I felt upset about being rejected after confessing to him but I don't think that's enough reason for me to want to take my own life. Falling into the water was an accident in the first place. Yet, you made it sound like suicide, as if you're afraid that others do not know that I killed myself for love. Tsk, I really can't clear my name now," Ye Li said, shrugging her shoulders helplessly. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“没写。”叶漓道。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201215T153936Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201215T153934Z">
        <seg>"I didn't write it," Ye Li answered.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“没听说啊，还跟咱们的文艺女神走在一起，肯定不是一般人吧？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T131734Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T131734Z">
        <seg>"Haven't you heard yet? She's walking beside the goddess of the arts. She definitely isn't an ordinary person, is she?"</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“眉儿，学校...”叶枫正想问学校关于那些流言的事情，就被叶旬扯了一下，他顿了顿，转了个语气问：“学校那边麻烦你帮老师说一声，阿漓可能要休息一段时间再过去。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T150946Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T150946Z">
        <seg>"Mei, the school..." Ye Feng was just about to question her about the rumors that had been spreading in school when Ye Xun tugged him. Ye Feng pause and continued with a different tone, "Please inform the teacher in school that Li has to rest and recuperate for some time before returning to school."</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“真是不要脸，还跑去自杀，她是不是因为咱们男神拒绝了她，所以才想要用这么极端的方式报复男神啊，太恶毒了吧！”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T134406Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T134406Z">
        <seg>"She's really shameless. She even tried to commit suicide. Did she think of using such an extreme way to retaliate against our idol because he had rejected her? How vicious!" </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“真是无脑脑残粉，尽是给自家偶像招黑，本来人家没那个意思，她非得要往那边想，现在好了吧，自己打自己的脸。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T170933Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T170933Z">
        <seg>"They're really brainless and retarded fans. All they do is garner haters for their idols. Ye Li didn't have those intentions in the first place but she insists on thinking that way. Great, now she's proven herself wrong." </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“等等，阿漓你怎么了，不爱吃没关系呀，我让厨房的人给你换就是了，怎么动这么大的火？再说了，这位厨师是我阿姨我特意给你招来的营养师，你之前不是还很喜欢他做的菜吗？”秦柔人如其名，柔声柔气的开口。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T144902Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T144502Z">
        <seg>"Wait, Li, what's the matter with you? It's okay if you don't like the food, I'll just get the chef to prepare something else. Why are you getting so angry? Besides, the chef is a nutrition I specially hired for you. Didn't you use to love the food she cooks?" Qin Rou asked tenderly, her voice as gentle as her name. [1. 'Rou' means 'gentle' in Chinese.] </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“肯定是，你们没看到她跟班长一起走进来的？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T184136Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T184136Z">
        <seg>"It must be her. Didn't you guys see that she had entered together with the class president?"</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“能有什么事情，全世界最好的医生都请回来了。”秦柔有些不屑，但话说的很小声。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T145834Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T145834Z">
        <seg>"What can happen to her? They've already hired the best doctors in the world," Qin Rou said softly with some disdain. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“行了，都别说了，让阿漓好好休息一下吧。”叶洛见妹妹脸色不大好看，开口道。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T142053Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T142053Z">
        <seg>"Okay, enough, let Li get some rest," Ye Luo said when he noticed that his younger sister looked a little unwell. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“让管家换个厨师。”叶漓将自家面前的营养餐推到了一边，站了起来，不容拒绝的说。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T144421Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T144411Z">
        <seg>"Get the butler to hire a new chef," Ye Li said assertively, pushing the nutritious meal away before standing up. She would not take no for an answer. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“转学生？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T182810Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T182810Z">
        <seg>"Is she a transfer student?"</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“这不就是你保持身材的好秘诀吗？我现在想减肥，自然得学着你一点，不然如何瘦的下去，你说是不是？”叶漓一脸天真的看她。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T150827Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T150819Z">
        <seg>"Isn't that your secret method for staying in shape? I want to lose weight now, so I naturally have to learn from you. Otherwise, how can I lose weight?" Ye Li said, looking at her innocently. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“这个合我胃口，你们谁都别跟我抢。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T183654Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T183654Z">
        <seg>"This one's my cup of tea, none of you vie with me."</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“这件事一直都是大家在猜想，若是她真那么喜欢于学长，这会儿肯定会借机缠上他才是，现在她却只想撇清关系，你们说会不会真的是误会了吗？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T164927Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T164927Z">
        <seg>"All this while, we have just been making speculations and wild guesses. If she really likes Senior Yu that much, she must have taken the chance to pester him. Yet, she just wants to cut off all relations to him and draw a line between them. Do you guys think that we've really mistaken them?" </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“这圆润的身材，摸着肯定很舒服。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T183135Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T183135Z">
        <seg>"It must be comfortable to touch her since she's soft and chubby."</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“这转折爱了爱了，没想到叶漓性格这么好，要是我，肯定都要打起来了。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T180407Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T180407Z">
        <seg>"I love this sudden twist. I didn't expect Ye Li to have such a good character. If I were in her shoes, I'd definitely fight her."</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“这难道就是传说中的不打不相识？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T180335Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T180335Z">
        <seg>"Is this the legendary theory where every friendship begins with hostility?" </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“那也不怪我，大家都这么说我才会这么以为的，刚刚你妹妹都还承认了，我才会要求你道歉，又不是我一个人的错！”见大家开始指责起了自己，那女同学脸色一阵涨红，恼怒的道。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T171123Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T171123Z">
        <seg>Seeing that everyone had begun blaming her, the girl felt embarrassed and infuriated. Flushed, she argued, "It's not my fault either. I only thought so because everyone said that it was the case. Just now, even your sister admitted it before I asked you to apologize, it's not solely my fault!" </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“那也得人家看的上你啊，我告诉你，这样的女孩子其实最难追。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T183718Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T183718Z">
        <seg>"Well, she has to like you too. I'm telling you, girls like her are actually the most difficult to woo." </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“那你的关心还真是让我害怕呢，我刚刚要是听你的承认了下来，估计等会就会成为全网暴力的对象了吧？啧啧，要不是你是我妹妹，我都要怀疑你是故意的。”叶漓一脸怀疑的说。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T165709Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T165650Z">
        <seg>"Well, your concern really scares me then. If I had just listened to you and admitted to it, I'd probably become the subject of cyber bullying later on, wouldn't I? Tsk, tsk, if you weren't my younger sister, I'd really suspect you were doing it on purpose," Ye Li said with a look of apprehension. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“那你的眼光还真挺独特，大家都觉得不好看，就你觉得好看。”叶漓若有所思的看她。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T153208Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T153208Z">
        <seg>"You've got a unique taste then. No one except you thinks that my previous hairstyle was nice," Ye Li said, looking at her ambiguously. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“那就好。”叶漓上了餐桌，看着自己面前的营养餐，皱了皱眉。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T142211Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T142211Z">
        <seg>"Good to hear." Ye Li walked to the desk and frowned after seeing the nutritious meal in front of her. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“那真是委屈你了。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T141542Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T141235Z">
        <seg>"You must be aggrieved." </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“都围在这里做什么，还不上课吗？”背后响起了老师不悦的声音，众人赶忙散开。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T180949Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T180949Z">
        <seg>"What are all of you crowding here for? Don't you have lessons?" the teacher chided in displeasure, after which the crowd quickly dispersed. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“阿姨不必这么麻烦，我看妹妹的营养师就不错，日后她吃什么，我就吃什么吧。”叶漓通情达理的道。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T150442Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T150442Z">
        <seg>"Auntie, you don't have to go to that trouble. I think Sister's nutritionist is great. From now on, I'll eat everything she does," Ye Li said in an understanding manner. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“阿漓你能想开最好。”愤怒的叶枫终究是无奈的叹了口气。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T142000Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T142000Z">
        <seg>"Li, it's good that you can figure it out and get over it."The infuriated Ye Feng sighed helplessly in the end. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“阿漓宝贝，你好好休息，这件事就交给哥哥们去查，一定不会让你白受了委屈，不要再想不开了好吗？有什么事情就告诉哥哥，但凡敢有人再说你半分，哥哥势必要让他后悔来到这个世界！”老三叶枫摸了摸妹妹的头，安抚着保证道。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T133625Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T133625Z">
        <seg>"Baby Li, rest well. Leave this matter to me and your brothers to investigate. I'll make sure you won't suffer for nothing. Don't be upset about it anymore, alright? If there's anything, just tell us about it. If anyone dares to criticize you again, I'll make sure he regrets being born in this world!" the third brother Ye Feng comforted his younger sister reassuringly while stroking her head. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“阿漓，你不要为难，哥哥们知道错了，不应该逼你，你不要有压力。”叶旬担忧的看着突然转变的妹妹，总感觉这次自杀之后，妹妹的性格变了。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T134733Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T134733Z">
        <seg>"Li Li, don't feel conflicted. We know that we're at fault for forcing you. Don't feel pressurized," Ye Xun said, looking worriedly at his younger sister who had a sudden change in attitude. He felt that her personality had changed after she tried to commit suicide. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“阿漓，你到底怎么了？哪里不舒服告诉哥哥们好吗？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T162828Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T162828Z">
        <seg>"Li, what's wrong with you? If you're feeling unwell, tell us, okay?"</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“阿漓，你终于醒了！”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T153516Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T153509Z">
        <seg>"Li, you've finally come to!" </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“阿漓，对不起，哥哥没想到他会这样对你。”叶枫猩红着一双眼，要不是他给自家妹妹介绍了于向阳，她也不会喜欢上他，最后被伤到这种境地。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T141236Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T141236Z">
        <seg>"Li, I'm sorry, I never thought he would treat you that way," Ye Feng said with bloodshot eyes. If he hadn't introduced Yu Xiangyang to his younger sister, she wouldn't have  fallen in love with him and ended up getting hurt to such an extent. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>“难道是我看错了？”秦柔柳叶眉微皱，觉得自己应该是想多了。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T145802Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T145802Z">
        <seg>"Were my eyes playing tricks on me?" Qin Rou muttered with a frown, feeling that she should have thought too much.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>【热！枫神&amp;心若向阳，昔日好兄弟反目当街动手！】</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T155705Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T155705Z">
        <seg>"Hot topic! Best Buddies God Feng and Beloved Xiangyang Turn Against Each Other And Fight On The Street!"</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>一个是娱乐圈当红大明星，一个是偶像剧男神，随便一个出一点事情，都会在网络上引起风浪的两个人，突然动起了手，大家自然是十分震惊。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T155954Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T155954Z">
        <seg>One was a famous celebrity in the entertainment industry while the other was a popular idol who often starred in idol dramas. Any incident that they were involved in would cause a huge uproar on the internet. Yet, both of them got into a fight. Everyone would naturally be astonished. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>一旁的叶眉见此场景，眸光一闪，无奈的道：“同学你别生气，我姐姐落水之后，脾气就有些不太好，她平时其实不是这样的。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T141741Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T141641Z">
        <seg>Standing at the side, Ye Mei's eyes glistened when she saw the scene and she said helplessly, "Schoolmate, don't be angry. Ever since my sister fell into the water, she has been hot-tempered. She isn't usually like this." </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>一群男生小声的议论起来。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T183741Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T183741Z">
        <seg>The group of boys began discussing amongst themselves softly.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>一群穿着改造过校服的精神小伙，正拿着手机不断的找寻猎物。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201210T133508Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201210T133508Z">
        <seg>Dressed in modified uniform, the group of energetic young men were continuously searching for prey. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>一股子淡淡的奶香飘过，徐晗挑了挑眉，目光落到了自己前面扎着高马尾的少女身上。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T191122Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T191122Z">
        <seg>A faint scent of milk wafted past and Xu Han raised his brows to look at the young girl in front of him who had her hair up in a ponytail. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>一行三人上了车。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T154402Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T154402Z">
        <seg>The trio got inside the car. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>一身白嫩如同婴儿一样的肌肤，在灯光的照射之下白到发光。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T165305Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T165305Z">
        <seg>She had supple and tender skin that was like that of a baby's and under bright light, it was fair and almost glowing. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>三个哥哥却没有注意到她的脸上变换的表情，因为刚刚叶漓那番话，都让三个男人几乎失去理智。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T180659Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T180659Z">
        <seg>However, Ye Li's brothers did not notice the change in her expression because the three of them had almost lost their rationality after hearing her words just now. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>三个哥哥离开之后，叶漓躺了回去。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T142340Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T142340Z">
        <seg>Ye Li lied down again after her three brothers left. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>三个哥哥都很优秀，都是人中之龙，可偏偏就她叶漓，干啥啥不行，犯错第一名。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T142547Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T142547Z">
        <seg>All three of her brothers were very outstanding and impeccable. However, unlike them, she was not good at anything at all, and was best at making mistakes. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>三个大男人随便一个出去，都是能掀起一阵风浪的风云人物。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T165339Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T165339Z">
        <seg>The three grown men were all powerful figures who could easily cause an uproar. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>三个男人对视一眼，都从彼此眼中看到了相同的想法。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T181638Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T181624Z">
        <seg>The three men looked at each other, and all saw the same thought in each other's eyes.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>三个男人看着她脸上翻腾的喜色，着实是觉得怪异。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T163129Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T163129Z">
        <seg>The three men found her joyous expression to be extremely bizarre. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>三个阴沉着一张脸站着的男人在看到女孩初醒的瞬间，一下围了上去，表情如出一辙的担忧。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T153928Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T153902Z">
        <seg>Three men with somber expressions immediately crowded the girl immediately after they saw her regaining consciousness. They all looked extremely worried. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>三人倒抽了一口气。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T140657Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T140657Z">
        <seg>The three men gasped. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>三人对视一眼，惊愕过后就是惊喜，“阿漓，你真的不怪我们了吗？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T133929Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T133929Z">
        <seg>The three of them looked at each other in shock, after which they said with some surprise and joy, "Li, do you really not blame us anymore?"</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>三人更是震惊，“你的意思是，你愿意跟徐凤年订婚？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T134449Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T134449Z">
        <seg>Greatly taken aback, the three of them asked, "Do you mean that you're willing to get engaged to Xu Fengnian?"</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>三人脸色铁青。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T181024Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T181024Z">
        <seg>The three of them turned pale. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>三人闻言，惊愕的看她。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T164946Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T164946Z">
        <seg>The three men looked at her in shock after hearing their words. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>三人闻言，顿时变脸：“什么？同学们嘲笑你？他们为什么要嘲笑你？谁敢嘲笑我们叶家的小公主，不想活了？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T174721Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T174721Z">
        <seg>Upon hearing her words, their expressions changed and they asked, "What? Your classmates mocked you? Why did they mock you? Who has the audacity to mock the little princess of the Ye Family? Do they have a death wish?" </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>三兄弟对视一眼，眸光中带着奇怪的光，叶洛沉声道：“不必，阿漓现在还很虚弱，你就不要上去打扰她了，有什么话留着明天说吧，我们还有事出去一趟，阿漓要是起来了，就通知我们。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T151340Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T151340Z">
        <seg>The three brothers looked at each other with peculiar gazes while Ye Luo said in a low voice, "You don't have to. Li is still very weak now, don't go upstairs to disturb her. If you have anything to tell her, save it for tomorrow. We have some matters to attend to so we're going out now. Inform us if Li wakes up."</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>三哥哥就更不用说了， 作为大明星的他，除了上课时间，其他的时间，行程都是排得满满的。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T173048Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T173048Z">
        <seg>On the other hand, her third brother was obviously busy as he was a famous celebrity. Apart from going to school, the rest of the time in his schedule would be fully lined up with activities. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>上辈子她所遭受的，必将要两人百倍奉还！</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T174100Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T174003Z">
        <seg>She would make them pay for all the suffering she had been through in her previous life, a hundredfold! </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>上辈子她最恨三位哥哥和爸爸，觉得是他们非要逼着自己嫁给徐凤年，毁了自己一辈子的幸福，所以一直对他们怀恨在心。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T160749Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T160749Z">
        <seg>In her previous life, she hated her three brothers and father the most for forcing her to marry Xu Fengnian and thus ruining her lifelong happiness. Hence, she had always born a grudge against them.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>上辈子好像就是有个男的，经常叫她小胖，她以为对方是辱骂自己，每一次听到都十分生气。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T191645Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T191645Z">
        <seg>In her previous life, there seemed to be a guy who often called her 'fatty' and she would get upset whenever she heard that because she thought that he was insulting her. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>上辈子的叶漓就很喜欢她的性子，甚至还曾希望过，要秦柔是她的妈妈就好了。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T145016Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T145010Z">
        <seg>In her previous life, Ye Li liked her temperament, and even wished that Qin Rou was her mother.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>上辈子自己自杀被救回来之后，本就对哥哥们恨到了极点，又听叶眉这话，直接把他们当仇人一样对待。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T140753Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T140753Z">
        <seg>In her previous life, she was filled with extreme hatred towards her brothers after she was rescued from her suicide attempt. When she heard Ye Mei's words, she treated them like her enemies. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>上辈子遭受了这一切的叶漓，性格也变得十分胆小自卑，甚至在叶眉的各种劝说之下，差点跑去医院整容。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T163452Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T163452Z">
        <seg>Ye Li, who had suffered all of that in her previous life, had also become extremely timid and she even developed an inferiority complex. In fact, she even almost went to the hospital to get plastic surgery under Ye Mei's various persuasions. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>下一秒，她的眼睛猛地睁开，扩散的瞳孔在一瞬间收缩，脸上还带着愤怒和惊恐绝望。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T153229Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T153229Z">
        <seg>In the next second, she opened her eyes abruptly and her dilated pupils constricted immediately while infuriation, panic, and despair were written all over her face. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>下定了决心，叶漓起身去了浴室洗漱。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T164556Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T164556Z">
        <seg>Having made up her mind, Ye Li got up and went to the bathroom to wash up.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>不同于叶眉的骨感美，她给人的感觉更惊艳耐看。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T182043Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T182043Z">
        <seg>Unlike Ye Mei who was beautifully thin, she looked stunning and her beautiful charm was long-lasting. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>不少同学们每天都会在校园门口蹲学校的诸位风云人物，亦或者是像是狗仔一样偷拍，然后发去贴吧或是微博，引起话题。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T164151Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T164151Z">
        <seg>Many students would squat in front of the campus every day to catch a glimpse of the famous figures in school or snap a series of photos of them like the paparazzi, which they would then upload onto the forum or Weibo to start a topic. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>不管如此，这辈子，她绝对不允许那样的事情发生了。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T173813Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T173813Z">
        <seg>No matter what, she would never allow that to happen again in this lifetime. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>不讨人喜欢不说，身材还差，好几次叶漓都在怀疑，自己是否亲生，不然为何家中随便一个都是颜值顶峰的强者，就她那般平凡？</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T142834Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T142834Z">
        <seg>Not only was she unlikable, she did not have a gorgeous figure either. On several occasions, Ye Li even suspected if she was their biological daughter. Otherwise, how could she have such ordinary looks when all the other members of her family were extremely good-looking? </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>不过今儿个的叶漓的打扮倒是出乎人的意料，仿佛换了一个人一般。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T181703Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T181703Z">
        <seg>However, Ye Li's appearance today had caught her off guard as she seemed like a completely different person. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>不过叶眉出了名的善良认识已近深入人心，大家虽然质疑，却也没有多想。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T170107Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T170107Z">
        <seg>However, Ye Mei's kind image was deeply rooted in their minds and although they were in doubt of her, they did not give it much thought. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>不过秦柔和叶眉都是聪明人，知道如何放低身份，也十分懂事，不吵不闹，这些年来倒是获取了不少人的好感。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T133114Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T133114Z">
        <seg>However, both Ye Mei and Qin Rou were smart enough to know how to swallow their pride, stay humble, behave themselves and not cause any trouble. Hence, over the years, they managed to get into the good books of many people. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>与此同时，一栋欧式豪华风格的别墅二楼，书房内，穿着白色衬衫的男人正坐在书桌前工作，他脖颈处的纽扣微微解开了两颗，从作者这个角度隐约可见的能看到几分肌肉线条，给男人增添了几分性感。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T145653Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T145653Z">
        <seg>At the same time, there was a man seated in front of a desk in the study on the second floor of a  European-style luxurious mansion, and doing some work. He was wearing a white shirt which had two unbuttoned buttons. The outline of his muscles could be seen vaguely, giving him a sexy, masculine charm. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>世界上最完美的三个男人，都是她的哥哥，最疼她最宠她，可上辈子的自己却恨了他们半辈子。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T164546Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T164546Z">
        <seg>The three most perfect men in the world were all her brothers, who loved and pampered her the most. However, in her previous life, she hated them for half a lifetime. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>两个觊觎自家家产的人，会那么为她着想？</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T143747Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T143747Z">
        <seg>How could two people who coveted her family's wealth be so concerned about her wellbeing? </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>两方原本和睦的粉丝纷纷在网上开始互相指责了起来，事情闹得很大，几乎一打开手机就是这个新闻。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T160118Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T160118Z">
        <seg>Their respective fanclubs which initially got along with each other harmoniously, began blaming each other and the matter soon escalated and got blown out of hand. The news were almost rampant and would show up on everyone's mobile phone. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>两方都没有出来澄清，这事大家也不知道到底是谁的错，也都在猜测着。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T160331Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T160331Z">
        <seg>Neither party came forth to clarify matters and no one knew who was at fault. They were all just making speculations. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>之前她对二小姐的话，可是唯命是从的，甚至只听得进去她的话，别人给的建议，她反倒是充其不闻。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T155616Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T155616Z">
        <seg>Previously, Ye Li had always went along with every suggestion Ye Mei made. In fact, Ye Mei was the only person she listened to and she would ignore ev everyone else's advice. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>之前就是因为脸大，所以叶漓才会留那么多的刘海，还天真的以为遮挡了大脸盆，就能漂亮。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T151757Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T151757Z">
        <seg>Previously, Ye Li decided to have bangs because of how large her face was. She even naively thought that she would look better with the bangs covering her face. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>之前自己这么叫她的时候，她都会十分生气。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T191820Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T191820Z">
        <seg>'When I called her that last time, she would get really mad at me.'</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>之前这个叶漓就经常不交论文，但是她都睁一只眼闭一只眼懒得管她。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201215T154557Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201215T154557Z">
        <seg>Previously, Ye Li often failed to submit her papers but Cheng Yan would usually just turn a blind eye to it as she could not be bothered to care about her. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>之后一家人的关系都降到了冰点。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T140827Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T140827Z">
        <seg>Afterwards, her relationship with her family became extremely strained. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>之后叶家出了事情，这些事情才缓缓露出水面。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T132105Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T132105Z">
        <seg>Later on, those matters were slowly uncovered because something happened to the Ye Family. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>之后叶漓的性情大变，从来没有受过这样委屈的她怎么可能忍受的了，为此还和老师吵了一架，便被人传播成了不良学生。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T163135Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T163026Z">
        <seg>After that, there was a drastic change in Ye Li's character. Since she had never been wronged and aggrieved before, how could she have tolerated it? She even got into an argument with the teacher because of that matter and everyone started calling her a delinquent. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>之后她对学校校草排行榜上第二名的于向阳纠缠不清之后，更是被全校人所嫌恶，那评论区的评论，都被癞蛤蟆想吃天鹅肉给刷屏了。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T162903Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T162903Z">
        <seg>Afterwards, she became obsessed with Yu Xiangyang, who was ranked second on the campus "Handsomest Boy" ranking, and got detested by all students in school. Most of the comments in the comment section were criticizing her for lusting over someone who was out of her league.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>之后秦家那边以孩子相逼，非要将秦柔母女送来，叶家碍于颜面，不得已才收了人。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T131326Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T131326Z">
        <seg>Afterwards, using the child as an excuse, the Qin Family insisted on sending Qin Rou and Ye Mei to the Ye Family. The Ye Family then had no choice but to accept them and take them in. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>乍一看不是那么惊艳，可仔细打量，却发现这女儿的五官真的是漂亮的不行。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T124622Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T124622Z">
        <seg>At first glance, she wasn't stunningly gorgeous but if one were to look closely at her, they would discover how beautiful her features were. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>也不知道她到底是太单纯，还是故意。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T170352Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T170352Z">
        <seg>'I wonder if she's too simple or just doing it on purpose.'</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>也不知道是谁偷拍了她的照片，放上了校园贴吧，还将叶眉的照片拿出来对比，一时之间，叶漓遭到了不少嘲笑的目光，成为了大家口中的热门笑话。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T162711Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T162711Z">
        <seg>Someone secretly took a photo of her and uploaded it onto the campus forum. They even compared it with Ye Mei's picture and all of a sudden, many people looked at Ye Li with mockery and she became a laughing stock and the talk of the town. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>也就是借助着大学积累的这些粉丝，还没毕业，就被不少娱乐大公司争相抢夺，最后同于向阳进了同一娱乐公司，迅速就发展成了一线明星。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T121713Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T121713Z">
        <seg>Relying on the fans she had gained in college, Ye Li shot to fame and many major entertainment companies vied with each other to sign her on. In the end, she entered the same entertainment company as Yu Xiangyang and developed rapidly into an A-list celebrity. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>也就是因为这样，圆润的叶漓就格外的显眼起来。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T184340Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T184340Z">
        <seg>That was also the reason that the chubby Ye Li became particularly eye-catching. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>也就是这样的态度，让叶漓注意到了对方，她是那种越是得不到就越是想要的人，更别说，从小到大，还没有她得不到的东西，于向阳的态度一下就激起了叶漓的逆反心理，对方越是拒绝，她就越不愿意放弃，暗地里打听了不少关于对方的事情，知道他的优秀之后便暗许了芳心，自此一发不可收拾。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T173429Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T173429Z">
        <seg>His aloof attitude was precisely the reason Ye Li paid attention to him. She was the type who would desperately want what she couldn't get. Besides, ever since she was a child, she would always get whatever she wanted. Yu Xiangyang's attitude immediately aroused Ye Li's rebellious spirit and the more resistant he was towards her, the more unwilling she was to give up. She secretly found out a lot of information about him and after she discovered how brilliant he was, she began to carry a torch for him. Since then, things went out of control. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>也正是因为很少会见到这三位哥哥，也导致了他们几个兄妹的关系越发的不亲近起来，倒是每天同叶眉上课下课，关系好得不得了。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T173233Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T173233Z">
        <seg>The fact that she rarely got to see her brothers was precisely the reason that the siblings began to grow distant from each other. Instead, Ye Li got extremely close to Ye Mei whom she went to school with everyday. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>也没听见他们总裁大人发怒的声音，众人疑惑看去，却见刚刚还认真看着文件的总裁，不知何时手中多了一个手机，他正一瞬不瞬的盯着屏幕看，好似还有些呆。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T172658Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T172658Z">
        <seg>They did not hear the angry holler of their esteemed CEO. They looked over in bewilderment and to their surprise, the CEO who had just been reading some documents attentively was suddenly holding his mobile phone and staring at the screen, seemingly spacing out too. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>于是她笑了笑说：“阿漓说的也是，是阿姨这边大意了，等会儿再去给你找几个会做的营养师过来，保准不会让你失望。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T145845Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T145845Z">
        <seg>Hence, she smiled and said, "Li, you're right. I was too careless. I'll look for a better nutritionist later. I promise you won't be disappointed." </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>于是疑惑的回头看他，也不说话。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T191440Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T191440Z">
        <seg>Hence, she turned around to look at him in bewilderment without saying anything.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>什么时候被人这般说过。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T180856Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T180856Z">
        <seg>Since when had she ever been criticized like this? </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>从小就没有母亲的她缺少母爱，是秦柔给了她这些，所以对她十分听话孝顺。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T145147Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T145147Z">
        <seg>Ever since she was a child, she lacked maternal love. Qin Rou was the one who showed her maternal love. Hence, she was very obedient and filial towards Qin Rou. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>从没注意过这个男人的声音这么好听。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T145140Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T145140Z">
        <seg>She had never paid attention to how pleasant his voice was. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>他不爱学习，成绩也不好，但是因为这张脸，与叶漓的情况大庭相反。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T185535Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T185535Z">
        <seg>He hated studying and had poor grades too but he was well-liked by the other students because of his good looks, unlike Ye Li. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>他们文艺系男生并不多，大多都是女孩子，而且这个年纪的女孩子都十分会控制身材，班上清一色的骨感美女。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T184325Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T184325Z">
        <seg>There were very few boys in the Faculty of Arts and most of the students were girls who at this age, paid a lot of attention to keeping themselves in shape. All the girls in class were thin beauties. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>他们疼爱的妹妹，自己从来不忍心说上一句狠话的宝贝疙瘩，竟然被外面的人这般欺辱！</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T180810Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T180810Z">
        <seg>Their beloved younger sister, whom they had never had the heart to be harsh towards, actually got bullied and horrendously insulted by outsiders! </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>他们胆子是大，但是也只是敢私下闹闹，哪里敢闹到警察局，到时候不仅是学校的人，就连家里的人都会被惊动！</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T171937Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T171937Z">
        <seg>Although they were bold, they only dared to confront others and stir trouble in private. They wouldn't dare to blow things up and go to the police station at all. If that were to happen, not only would the people in school be alerted, even her family members would be informed!</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>他们记得没错的话，家里和小妹同一个学校的就只有叶眉了吧。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T181656Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T181656Z">
        <seg>If they remembered correctly, Ye Mei was the only one in the family who went to the same school as their younger sister. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>他们这些大家族的一举一动都能引起整个城市的动荡，所以对于这些大事，一向都是十分的隐秘，只有自家的人和少许关系好的人才会知道。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T181349Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T181349Z">
        <seg>They were powerful and influential families who could easily cause a stir in the entire city. Hence, they had always been secretive about such events. Only their own family members and a small, select group of people whom they were close to would find out. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>他叫徐晗，年龄二十，身高一米八五，身材很好，十分喜欢各种极限运动，家里十分有钱，随便一双球鞋都是七位数，因为一张篮球照在学校出名，成为了不少女孩倾慕暗恋的对象。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T185505Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T185505Z">
        <seg>His name was Xu Han. He was 20 years old this year, and had a good figure, with a stature of 1.85 meters. He was particularly fond of all kinds of extreme sports, and coming from an extremely affluent family, every pair of shoes that belonged to him would easily cost seven figures. After he rose to fame because of a photo of him playing basketball, many girls in school adored him and developed crushes on him. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>他娘的，刚还一副剑拔弩张的模样，这才几分钟呢，就一副相见恨晚，恨不得拜把子了。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T180103Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T180103Z">
        <seg>'Damn it, she was so haughty and arrogant just now but it's only been a few minutes and she's already regretting her actions.'</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>他成熟又完美，是年轻一代的佼佼者，可就是这样的男人，却是一个妹控！</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T163612Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T163612Z">
        <seg>He was mature and perfect, and a leader of the younger generation. However, a powerful man like him actually doted on his younger sister greatly!  </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>他收回了目光，冷漠的点了点头。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T150610Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T150559Z">
        <seg>He looked away and nodded indifferently. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>他是她三哥哥叶枫的朋友，两人关系不错，都在娱乐圈混的风生水起，不同的是，于向阳的家室并不好，但是他却是学校为数不多知道叶漓身份的人之一。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T172831Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T172831Z">
        <seg>He was a close friend of her third brother, Ye Feng, and had rose to fame in the entertainment industry with the latter. However, unlike Ye Feng, Yu Xiangyang did not come from a wealthy and powerful family. Yet, he was one of the few people in school who knew about Ye Li's true identity. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>他气质慵懒，白色的衬衫有些凌乱，头发都是乱糟糟的，可偏偏这样的形象，非但没有给人一丝邋遢的感觉，竟然还莫名的帅气。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T185110Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T185110Z">
        <seg>He looked rather sluggish and laid back, his white shirt a little messy, just like his hair. However, he did not look disheveled or sloppy at all. Instead, he seemed somewhat handsome. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>他这么一说，叶漓突然就想起来了。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T191612Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T191612Z">
        <seg>After hearing his words, Ye Li suddenly remembered something. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>以前她的性格冲动，叶眉越这么说 ，她就越是生气，越是要去帮她讨回公道。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T141846Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T141846Z">
        <seg>In the past, she was impulsive and reckless. The more Ye Mei turned down her offer, the more she would want to do Ye Mei justice and stand up for her. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>以前的叶漓总是用一头浓密的头发遮住脸，给人的第一眼就不好看，也没有人多注意过她，就连拍的照片都只露出了个下巴，平时学校的人那么多，大家亲眼见过的也不多，不是很熟的人还真没有认出来。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T132043Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T132043Z">
        <seg>In the past, Ye Li used to cover her face with her thick hair and at first glance, she looked rather unpleasant and no one paid much attention to her. Even in pictures, she would only reveal her chin. Many students in school had seen her in person before but only those who were close to her would be able to recognize her. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>以至于学习成绩一直都是在班级排名倒数，大家就以为她是学习很差的那一类人。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T161003Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T161003Z">
        <seg>Besides, her academic results had always been at the bottom of the ranks in her class. Hence, everyone thought that she was a student with poor grades. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>仿佛像是看一个陌生人。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T141107Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T141107Z">
        <seg>She seemed to be a stranger.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>众人上上下下的打量着叶漓，惊喜的发现这个女孩长相虽然圆润的紧，但是通身气质清冷高贵，那双微微向上挑的狐狸眼，给人一种又纯又欲的感觉。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T183525Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T183525Z">
        <seg>Everyone sized Ye Li up from head to toe and they were surprised to find that although she was extremely plump, she had a sophisticated and noble aura, and her slightly upturned foxy eyes were innocent yet seductive. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>众人不禁有些怀疑起了事情的真相。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T165252Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T165252Z">
        <seg>Everyone could not help but be a little suspicious of the truth of the matter.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>众人也是有些怪异的看向叶眉。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T165726Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T165726Z">
        <seg>Everyone else looked at Ye Mei with bewildered expressions as well. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>众人大脑嗡的一声，只觉得这是谁，要完了！</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T172518Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T172518Z">
        <seg>There was a sudden buzzing in everyone's heads and they thought, 'Who's this? Oh dear!'</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>众人奇异的看着这一幕，仿佛见了鬼。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T172732Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T172732Z">
        <seg>Everyone looked at this scene in bewilderment, as if they had seen a ghost. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>众人将锅甩到了叶眉身上。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T180732Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T180732Z">
        <seg>Everyone put the blame on Ye Mei. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>众人小声的议论纷纷起来，刚刚还对叶漓改变的惊讶，逐渐变成了嫌恶。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T133334Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T133334Z">
        <seg>The people around them began discussing one after another. The shock that they had from seeing the changes in Ye Li's expression, gradually turned into disgust. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>众人怜悯的目光落到了叶漓身上，</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T170408Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T170408Z">
        <seg>Everyone cast looks of sympathy at Ye Li. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>众人愣住了。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T164744Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T164744Z">
        <seg>Everyone was stunned. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>众人的态度纷纷倒戈。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T171010Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T171010Z">
        <seg>Everyone's attitudes immediately became reversed. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>众人的目光一下落到了她的身上。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201215T153843Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201215T153843Z">
        <seg>All eyes were immediately on her. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>众人看着这神一般的转折，呆愣到了极点。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T180033Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T180033Z">
        <seg>Everyone was dumbfounded when they saw the sudden change. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>众人说到这里，顿时义愤填膺的看向叶漓，那目光好似要吃人一般，“叶漓，看在你妹妹的份儿上，这事情我们就不找你麻烦了，但是你必须得站出来当面承认，你自杀的事情跟我们男神没有关系！不然我们一心向阳粉绝对不会放过你的！”有女生站了出来，威胁叶漓道。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T134855Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T134855Z">
        <seg>At the mention of this, they immediately looked at Ye Li menacingly with righteous indignation, as if they wanted to eat her up. "Ye Li, for the sake of your sister, we won't hold you accountable for this matter. However, you must come forth and admit that your attempt at suicide has nothing to do with our idol! Otherwise, we, the fans of Xiangyang, will never let you off!" a girl threatened Ye Li. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>众人都不是傻子，稍稍仔细一想，就察觉到了这其中的怪异之处。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T170035Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T170035Z">
        <seg>The people were no fools and after thinking about it carefully, they noticed the peculiarity of the matter. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>众人面面相觑一眼，都从对方的眼中看到了深意。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T170254Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T170254Z">
        <seg>Everyone looked at each other in puzzlement, and noticed the hidden meaning in each other's eyes.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>但她性格好，人优秀，又是学霸，在学校女神排行榜排名前五，班级排名第一，出了名的清纯女神。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T161139Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T161139Z">
        <seg>However, she had a brilliant personality and was a star student. Hence, she was ranked in the top five of the "College Goddess" rankings, and was first in her class. She was known for being a pure and innocent goddess-like girl. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>但是不能会因为不好，就不去了。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T163737Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T163737Z">
        <seg> </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>但是今年，却是至关重要的一年。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T142434Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T142434Z">
        <seg>However, this year was a crucial one. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>但是去医院的照片却不知道被谁拍到，发到了学校网上，自此之后，她又背上了一个整容之名。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T163627Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T163627Z">
        <seg>However, someone happened to snap some photos of her going to the hospital and uploaded it to the campus website. Since then, she was labeled as the girl who wanted to go for plastic surgery. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>但是叶漓却十分出名。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T161355Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T161355Z">
        <seg>However, Ye Li was exceptionally famous because of Ye Li. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>但是既然阿漓说了，那必定就是这知事人中其中之一，而他们最熟悉的，无非就是叶眉，于向阳还有叶枫的那几个好兄弟。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T155505Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T155318Z">
        <seg>However, since Ye Li had already said so, Ye Mei must be one of the people who knew about the matter. Besides, Ye Mei, Yu Xiangyang, and Ye Feng's close friends were the ones whom they were the most familiar with.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>但是程艳就不这么想了。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201215T154425Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201215T154425Z">
        <seg>However, Cheng Yan thought otherwise. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>但是这可不是叶眉想要看到的。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T152513Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T152513Z">
        <seg> </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>但是这段时间，这个学生闹的事情确实太多，连带着老师们都被惊动了，她这个导师还跟着被人笑话！</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201215T154625Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201215T154625Z">
        <seg>However, Ye Li had gotten into plenty of trouble lately and even they, the teachers, were alarmed. She was seen as a laughing stock just because she was Ye Li's teacher!</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>但这也是因为家里人过度的宠溺所致，她又是易胖体质，长得也不高，矮矮胖胖的，同学们都叫她小肥妞。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T143120Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T143118Z">
        <seg>However, that was also the reason that her family members spoiled her and overindulged her. She was the type to gain weight easily and was short in stature. Due to the fact that she was short and chubby, her classmates all called her 'fatty'.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>偏偏叶漓就拉低了整个班的档次。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T184833Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T184833Z">
        <seg>However, Ye Li pulled down the level of her class. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>偏偏这样一双魅惑至极的双眼，竟然长在了这样一张圆润的脸蛋上。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T170147Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T170147Z">
        <seg>Yet, her beautiful and charming pair eyes were actually matched with her round and chubby face. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>光是他们系，学校榜上排名前十的风云人物就有两个，一个叶眉，一个徐晗。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T190301Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T190301Z">
        <seg>There were two students from their faculty who made it to the top ten influential figures of the campus. One was Ye Mei, and the other was Xu Han. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>其中一少年手中的手机下意识对上了叶漓的脸，盯着屏幕中的人儿啧啧称赞。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T123628Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T123624Z">
        <seg>One of the young men subconsciously pointed the camera of his mobile phone at Ye Li's face, praising her continuously while admiring her beauty.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>其他人闻声，顿时看了过去。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201210T134221Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201210T134221Z">
        <seg>The others heard the sound and looked over immediately.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>其实订婚这件事本是秘密，可不知被谁透露了出去，以至于同学们嘲笑她小小年纪就要给什么老总当未婚妻。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T170436Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T170436Z">
        <seg>Actually, the engagement was originally supposed to be a secret but it somehow got leaked by someone, thus causing her to be ridiculed by her classmates  for being the fiancée of a CEO at such a young age.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>再加上今儿个是自己来找人家麻烦，她就是全责，到时候不是惨了吗？</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T172017Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T172017Z">
        <seg>Besides, she ought to bear the full responsibility because she had confronted Ye Li by herself. If the police got involved, wouldn't she face dire consequences? </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>再加上她同叶眉从小一起长大，两人关系一直很好，她几乎是对她的话深信不疑。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T180017Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T180017Z">
        <seg>Besides, she grew up together with Ye Mei and the two of them had always been the best of friends. She almost never doubted her words. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>再看看周围的粉红色的豪华装饰的房间，她愣住了。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T155538Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T155538Z">
        <seg>Looking around at the luxuriously decorated room that had pink as its theme color, she was dumbfounded. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>再说叶漓这一边，刚上教学楼，就有不少人盯着她的方向看，当然，看得人不是她，是一旁的叶眉。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T131234Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T131234Z">
        <seg>On the other hand, as soon as Ye Li entered the teaching building, many people began looking in her direction. Of course, they were not looking at her but Ye Mei. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>几个像是老婆子般一直劝导的男人闻声一下就闭了嘴，疑惑的对视一眼，便道：“你这丫头，傻了不成，2020年5月23号啊。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T162310Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T162310Z">
        <seg>The men, who had been persuading her like old long-winded women, immediately fell silent after hearing her words. They looked at each other in bewilderment before saying, "Silly girl, it's the 23rd of May, 2020."</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>几个少年手一抖，手中的手机差点就掉在了地上。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T125244Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T125244Z">
        <seg>The hands of the few young men trembled and they almost dropped their mobile phones. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>几乎是人人艳羡的代表人物，男人心中的清纯女神。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T171132Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T171132Z">
        <seg>She was almost the subject of everyone's envy and the pure and innocent goddess in the hearts of all the guys. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>几人愣住，随后对视一眼，都从对方眼中看到了相同的担忧之色，戴着眼镜穿着白衬衫十分精明的男人严肃的开口：“你这是说什么傻话，你怎么可能会死呢？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T154544Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T154544Z">
        <seg>The few men were stunned, after which they looked at each other and saw the looks of worry in one another's eyes. The smart man who was wearing glasses and a white shirt chastised sternly, "What silly things are you saying? How can you be dead?" </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>几人抬起的脚在空中一顿。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T130607Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T130607Z">
        <seg>The few of them paused in their tracks, their legs in midair. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>别说是外人，就连叶眉也是一脸惊愕的看着叶漓。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T141046Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T141046Z">
        <seg>Even Ye Mei was looking at Ye Li in exasperation, let alone the outsiders. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>到了最后才明白，年纪轻轻就出了意外的哥哥们，才是真正关心她的人。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T161038Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T161038Z">
        <seg>She only realized in the end that her brothers who had gotten into an accident at a young age, were the ones who really cared about her.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>到底是何方神圣给他们总裁大人发消息啊，竟然能让雷厉风行的大总裁发呆。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T172814Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T172814Z">
        <seg>'Who sent the CEO a message? He or she actually managed to make the austere and domineering CEO space out.'</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>前段时间她跳河自杀一事，闹的沸沸扬扬。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T163119Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T163119Z">
        <seg>Previously, she caused an uproar when she tried to commit suicide by jumping into the river. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>前面憨厚的司机到这话，还好奇的从后视镜看了叶漓一眼，随后笑着夸赞：“我也觉得挺好看的，精神。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T153251Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T153251Z">
        <seg>When the daft chauffeur in front heard those words, he even curiously looked at Ye Li from the rearview mirror, then smiled and praised, "I think you look great too. You look much more energetic." </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>印象中的叶漓，向来都是低着头，只对人露出一个下巴。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T181348Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T181348Z">
        <seg>In her memory, Ye Li had always hung her head low and would only reveal her chin to others. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>即使大家知道不好接触，但是越是这样难以攻略的人，越是有人愿意飞蛾扑火。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T190053Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T190053Z">
        <seg>Even though everyone knew that it was hard to get along with him, the harder he was to conquer, the more they were willing to try.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>即使身材微胖，也并没有拉低她的颜值。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T124655Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T124655Z">
        <seg>Even though she was chubby, it did not affect her beauty. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>原本吵闹的教室一瞬间像是失去了声音。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T182542Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T182542Z">
        <seg>The boisterous classroom immediately fell silent. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>原本脸色不大好的她一下看起来就精致了不少，薄薄的刘海儿隐约露出她细长的眉毛，微微上挑的眼尾硬生生的给这张脸增添了几分诱惑，特别是眼角下还有一颗泪痣。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T165554Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T165554Z">
        <seg>Ye Li, who originally looked sickly, now looked much more exquisite than before. Her thin bangs revealed her long and thin eyebrows, and the slightly upturned corners of her eyes made her look attractive, especially with the mole under the corner of the eye.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>原来如此，原来如此。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T140706Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T140706Z">
        <seg>So that's what happened. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>又a又飒！</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T125219Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T125219Z">
        <seg>It was suave!</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>另一边，完全不知道自己打扰了人家开会的叶漓已经背上了自己的书包下了楼。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T172834Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T172834Z">
        <seg>On the other hand, Ye Li, who was completely unaware that she had just disrupted the meeting, had already gone downstairs with her schoolbag. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>另一边，帝国集团会议室中。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T172432Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T172045Z">
        <seg>On the other hand, there was an oppressive tension in the air of the conference room of Empire Group conglomerate at this moment. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>只可惜这徐晗来上课那是看心情。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T190448Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T190448Z">
        <seg>Unfortunately, Xu Han would decide whether to turn up for class or not, depending on his mood. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>只恨自己瞎了眼，一心只相信叶眉和于向阳这对渣男贱女的话，以至于最后被害到了那样的下场！</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T160956Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T160956Z">
        <seg>She could only blame herself for being blind and believing Yu Xiangyang and Ye Mei, the despicable couple who caused her to end up in that terrible situation!</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>只是不同的是，徐凤年没有让叶眉得逞过。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T132313Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T132303Z">
        <seg>However, the difference was that Xu Fengnian had never let Ye Mei gotten what she wanted. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>只是不知道，你这个位置还能坐多久呢？</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T171144Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T171144Z">
        <seg>'But how long can you be in this position for?'</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>只是今天这三兄弟的表情有些奇怪，让她摸不着头脑。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T154304Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T154304Z">
        <seg>However, her three brothers had strange expressions today which confused her. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>只是他们的目光从叶眉身上扫过之后，都好奇的落到了叶漓身上，见是一张陌生人的脸，纷纷疑惑：“那人是谁啊，艺术系又来新人了吗？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T131339Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T131339Z">
        <seg>However, after looking away from Ye Mei, they glanced at Ye Li curiously. Feeling bewildered by the fresh face, she asked, "Who's that person? Is there a new student in the Faculty of Arts?"</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>只是奈何叶眉出来帮忙，那些人才不好对她动手。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T163014Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T163014Z">
        <seg>However, Ye Mei stood up to help her, so those people found it inappropriate to hit her. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>只是想着秦柔这么关心自己，自己却不顺从着她的话，好像是不太好，所以即使是不喜欢，也装出了一副很满意的模样。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T145450Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T145450Z">
        <seg>However, she used to comply and pretend that she was pleased with the meals because she felt that it would be inappropriate to defy Qin Rou who had always showed her concern and doted on her. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>只是胖的比较慢，叶漓并没有放心上，只当是因为自己平时贪吃导致，从来没有往其他地方联想。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T143655Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T143655Z">
        <seg>However, Ye Li did not pay much attention to her weight gain because it was slow and gradual. She simply thought that it was caused by her gluttony and penchant for eating. Hence, she did not think of other reasons.  </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>只是自家哥哥一举一动都很容易被狗仔拍到，更别说这样劲爆的大新闻。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T160252Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T160234Z">
        <seg>However, the paparazzi would easily capture every single move of her brother. Besides, the news this time was groundbreaking. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>只是这对于已经二十八岁的叶漓来说，简直就是上天的恩赐。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T170303Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T170303Z">
        <seg>However, that was a gift from God Ye Li, who was already 28 years old.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>只是，叶眉虽然同他们是同父异母，关系不是很亲，但是从小乖巧，也是三人看着长大的人，怎么也不敢想她会传播出这样的事情。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T181836Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T181836Z">
        <seg>Although Ye Mei was their half-sister whom they were not very close to, they had watched her grow up and she had always been obedient since she was a child. They never expected that she would spread the news about this matter. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>可一旦叶漓承认了，被人发到了网上，那她即将承受的，可不仅仅是同学们的怒火，而是于向阳那几百万的粉丝的疯狂报复。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T165859Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T165859Z">
        <seg>However, once Ye Li admitted it and the matter was posted on the Internet, she would immediately have to suffer the revenge of Yu Xiangyang's millions of fans, in addition to the rage of her classmates. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>可不管是不是，自家的妹妹不能白受了这个委屈。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T181905Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T181905Z">
        <seg>However, regardless of whether she was the one who spread it or not, they would never let their younger sister be mistreated that way. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>可为什么？</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T160056Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T160047Z">
        <seg>'But why?'</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>可二十岁之后，家中的人因为已故母亲当初同好姐妹徐家大夫人曾定下的娃娃亲，非要让她同那个冷冰冰的男人订婚，彼时，叶漓已近有了心仪之人，又怎会愿意。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T161640Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T161640Z">
        <seg>After Ye Li reached the age of twenty, her family insisted that she marry the cold and unfeeling man from the Xu Family, because her late mother had betrothed her to the son of her best friend, the matriarch of the Xu Family, ever since they were children. However, Ye Li was already in love with someone else. How could she have agreed to it?  </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>可今儿个是怎么了，一直帮着外人说话，让叶漓道歉，还变相的告诉大家，就是叶漓的错，真是奇了怪了。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T144210Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T144119Z">
        <seg>However, she seemed to be continuously standing up for outsiders today and making Ye Li apologize. That was indirectly telling others that it was Ye Li's fault, which was rather strange. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>可低垂的眸中，却带着几分疑惑。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T151446Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T151446Z">
        <seg>However, there was some puzzlement in her eyes when she was looking down. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>可具体到底是哪里出了变了，她也看不出来。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T160247Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T160243Z">
        <seg>However, she could not put a finger on what exactly changed. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>可刚刚她却那样做了，是真的因为担心，还是别有用意？</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T165958Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T165958Z">
        <seg>However, she actually did that just now. Was she really just worried or does she have an ulterior motive?</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>可到了最后才知道，原来自己最讨厌的人，才是真正宠她入骨的。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T160842Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T160842Z">
        <seg>However, she only found out in the end that the people whom she hated the most were actually the ones who truly spoiled her to bits. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>可却没想到，自己遭受的这一切，都是她在背后所策划。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T163102Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T163102Z">
        <seg>However, she didn't expect that Ye Mei was the one who caused all her torment. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>可叶漓这么一说，大家顿时就感觉到了另一层的深意。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T144552Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T144552Z">
        <seg>However, once Ye Li said so, everyone immediately felt that there was another meaning to her words. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>可在妹妹面前，他们却卑微到了骨子里。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T165544Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T165527Z">
        <seg>However, in front of their younger sister, they would swallow their pride and were extremely humble. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>可实际那样的发型在现在这个时代，是最土的。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T151847Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T151847Z">
        <seg>However, in this current day and age, her previous hairstyle was already outdated and tacky.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>可对于如今的她又不是傻子。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T143703Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T143703Z">
        <seg>However, she was no longer a fool. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>可就是这样一个男人，在自己失去一切之后，当着所有记者的面说和她不熟。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T173603Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T173603Z">
        <seg>However, he was also the same man who told all the reporters that he did not know her well after she lost everything. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>可当他们看到叶漓坐到最后那个位置的时候，说这话的嘴巴都不约而同的停了下来。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T183803Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T183803Z">
        <seg>However, when they saw Ye Li sitting down at her seat, they stopped unanimously. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>可惜依旧记不得叫什么了，就感觉对方突然走到她的身后坐下，那动静大的直接掀起了一阵风，吹乱了她的发丝。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T191052Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T191052Z">
        <seg>Unfortunately, she could no longer remember their names and she felt that he had suddenly walked over and sat down behind her. His actions caused a gust of wind to blow up and mess up her hair. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>可旁边这个，是叶漓？</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T181050Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T181050Z">
        <seg>'Is this girl beside her Ye Li?'</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>可是想到刚刚自己还偷偷骂过人家，这会是怎么也不好意思惦着脸上去说话。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T180559Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T180559Z">
        <seg>However, at the thought of the fact that they had just secretly scolded Ye Li just now, they found it too embarrassing to go forth and speak to her. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>可此时男人冷峻的脸上，却带着几分惊愕，他手中的手机，差点就因耳旁响起的那一句话，从手中滑落.....</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T145745Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T145745Z">
        <seg>However, there was some shock on his handsome face now. He almost dropped his mobile phone that he was holding in his hand, because of the alarming words of hers... </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>可现在，她暗暗冷笑，垂眸看了某个男人发来的消息一眼，回道：“是吗？我觉得挺好看的呀。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T151951Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T151940Z">
        <seg>However, now, she sneered and looked down to take a glance at the text message that she received from a certain man. "Is that so? I think it looks great." </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>可眼前这个女孩子，虽然胖是胖，但是给人的感觉却完全不一样。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T184857Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T184854Z">
        <seg>Although the girl in front of them was chubby, she gave off a completely different vibe.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>可确实，当时她没有在现场， 并不知道到底发生了什么，也只是听说而已，谁料想今天的叶漓竟然这么会说，三言两语就把自己洗白了，她如今和叶漓关系还好，再说下去，恐是会让她怀疑。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T165432Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T165432Z">
        <seg>However, it was true that she wasn't at the scene at the time and had no idea what happened. She had merely heard everything based on hearsay. To her surprise, Ye Li actually said those words today and effortlessly cleared her own name. Her relationship with Ye Li was still cordial for now and if she went on to talk about that, she might really arouse Ye Li's suspicion. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>可覆水难收，她对他的误会太深，恨意早已压垮了那仅仅剩余的一丝情谊。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T144531Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T144531Z">
        <seg>However, what was done could not be undone. She had misunderstood him greatly in the past and her hatred for him had already overwhelmed the last bit of feelings that she had for him.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>可这个没什么记忆的少年，却精准的认出她？</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T191407Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T191407Z">
        <seg>Yet, this young man whom she had a vague impression of, actually managed to recognize her accurately. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>可这也改变不了，她之前传出来的那些丑闻。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T133448Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T133448Z">
        <seg> </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>可这件事距离此时已近过去了八年，又怎会再现？</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T162042Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T162042Z">
        <seg>However, it had been eight years since that incident occurred. Why did this scene appear again? </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>可这会儿平淡的像是什么也没发生一般，根本就没将这个称呼放在心上。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T191841Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T191841Z">
        <seg>'But this time, she's so composed, like nothing had happened. She doesn't take it to heart at all.'</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>可这对他们来说，却更为反常，不由的担忧对视一眼，作为大哥的叶洛先开了口，“阿漓，让你和徐凤年订婚是我们的不对，以后万不可再做傻事了好不好？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T165304Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T165304Z">
        <seg>However, to them, they felt that she was acting out of the ordinary. They couldn't help but look at each other worriedly. The eldest brother, Ye Luo, was the first to speak. "Li, it was wrong of us to make you get engaged to Xu Fengnian back then. Don't do anything stupid in the future again, alright?" </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>可这幅怪异的表情落到三人眼中，又是一阵疑惑。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T160251Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T160150Z">
        <seg>However, the three men were confused again when they saw her peculiar expression. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>可这样一个男人，在知道她身份之后，竟然也不像是其他人那样讨好她顺着她，甚至对她嗤之以鼻，冷漠相对。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T172938Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T172938Z">
        <seg>However, after discovering her identity, a man like him actually despised her and treated her coldly with disdain and contempt, unlike others who tried hard to please her and get into her good books. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>可那样太奇怪了，重生也太奇怪了，她必须得忍住，直到确定一切都是真实存在为止。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T164928Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T164928Z">
        <seg>However, that was too strange, just like her rebirth. She had to hang on until she was certain that everything was real.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶旬同叶枫也是一脸紧张又小心翼翼的看着她。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T165320Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T165320Z">
        <seg>Ye Xun and Ye Feng also looked at her nervously and cautiously. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶旬和叶枫一下就闭了嘴，点了点，一步三回头的和她告别。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T142321Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T142321Z">
        <seg>Ye Xun and Ye Feng immediately kept quiet and nodded. While leaving, they continuously turned around to look at her. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶旬点了点头，与他如出一辙的表情。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T182008Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T182008Z">
        <seg>Ye Xun nodded with the same expression as him.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶旬蹙着眉头：“阿漓都说了，那些话是从他们班上传出去，但是她们班上，只有叶眉知道这件事。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T155252Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T155252Z">
        <seg>With a frown, Ye Xun said, "Li has already said that those rumors were spread from her class. In their class, no one except Ye Mei knows about this." </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶枫不敢置信，毕竟于向阳和他是好兄弟，关系也非常不错，平时虽然话不多，但是于向阳一向彬彬有礼，和谁都相处的好，怎，怎么会私下那样说他的妹妹？</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T140407Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T140407Z">
        <seg>Ye Feng was in disbelief. After all, Yu Xiangyang was his close friend and they were on extremely good terms with each other. Although Yu Xiangyang was not talkative, he had always been a well-mannered person who was polite and courteous to everyone. Why would he say that about Ye Li in private? </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶枫有些疑惑，“二哥，刚刚你为什么不让我问，眉儿和阿漓同个班级，她应该知道才对，虽然这件事一直保密，但是保不准会被谁透露出去也不是没这个可能。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T154451Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T154451Z">
        <seg>Feeling a little confused, Ye Feng asked, "Second Brother, why didn't you let me ask Mei just now? Since Mei is in the same grade as Li, she should be well aware. Although this matter has been kept secret, it is possible that someone has leaked it." </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶枫沉默了。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T155610Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T155610Z">
        <seg>Ye Feng was silent. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶枫点了点头。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T151114Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T151114Z">
        <seg>Ye Feng nodded.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶枫脸色薄怒，“这件事还没确定，那些人怎么会知道？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T181100Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T181029Z">
        <seg>Ye Feng's face was full of anger. "This matter hasn't been confirmed yet. How would those people know?"</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶洛和叶旬两兄弟对视一眼，同样想到了这个问题。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T181137Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T181137Z">
        <seg>Ye Xun and Ye Luo looked at each other as they had also thought of the same problem.  </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶洛的目光从叶眉担忧的脸上扫过。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T150537Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T150520Z">
        <seg>Ye Luo glanced at the worried Ye Mei. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶漓不屑的表情不似作假，难道真的是他们误会了吗？</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T164814Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T164814Z">
        <seg>Ye Li's disdainful expression did not seem fake at all. Thus, they wondered if they had really misunderstood everything. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶漓不说这个问题，没人会多想，都觉得叶眉好像是在帮她说话。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T144522Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T144522Z">
        <seg>If Ye Li did not bring up that issue, no one else would think much of it and they would all feel that Ye Mei seemed to be speaking up for her. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶漓乖巧的点了点头，十分歉意的说：“对不起，大哥二哥三哥，之前是我太任性了，还总是跟你们闹不是，你们不要生阿漓的气好不好？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T133805Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T133805Z">
        <seg>Ye Li nodded obediently and said apologetically, "I'm sorry, Eldest Brother, Second Brother, Third Brother, I was too willful and capricious back then. I kept throwing tantrums at you guys. Don't be angry at me, alright?"</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶漓也不在乎，反正现在大家对她的印象都很差，不喜欢也是正常，她也不勉强，只是那个论文，她还真不记得了，算了吧，不交了。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T182449Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T182449Z">
        <seg>Ye Li could not be bothered either. Anyway, everyone had a poor impression of her now and it was normal that she was disliked by many. She did not try to force it. However, she really couldn't remember anything about the paper so she decided to forget it and just not submit it. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶漓以为离开了徐凤年，自己就可以重新开始。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T180547Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T180547Z">
        <seg>Ye Li thought that she could start anew after leaving Xu Fengnian.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶漓伸手捏住了棒棒糖，口中弥漫的甜腻让她眯了眯眼，微微抬眸，冷冽的目光扫向说话的女同学，嘲讽的扯了扯嘴角：“你是以什么身份跟我说话？于向阳的女朋友？还是他妈？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T135922Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T135922Z">
        <seg>Ye Li reached out to grab her lollipop and squinted as the sweetness filled her mouth. She looked up a little and stared coldly at the female student who had been talking. She smirked sneeringly and asked, "In what position are you talking to me? Yu Xiangyang's girlfriend? Or his mother?"</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶漓低垂着眸，突然又来了一句。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T181604Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T181604Z">
        <seg>Ye Li looked down and suddenly said those words. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶漓关了新闻，从床上起身。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T160341Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T160336Z">
        <seg>Ye Li turned off the news channel and got up from the bed.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶漓冷冷一笑，一脸讽刺：“现在你又搞得好像是我欺负了你一样，明明就是你和一个外人逼我承认这件事，怎么反倒是先委屈起来了呢？该委屈的是我吧？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T163954Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T163954Z">
        <seg>Ye Li sneered and said with a look of sarcasm, "Now you're making it seem like I bullied you. You were obviously the one who colluded with an outsider to force me to admit to this. Why are you feeling wronged and aggrieved instead? I should be the one feeling that way, aren't I?"</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶漓听到众人的惊呼声，抬眸扫了一眼就收回了目光。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T190853Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T190853Z">
        <seg>When Ye Li heard everyone gasping and swooning, she looked up before turning away quickly. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶漓呵呵笑了两声。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T153258Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T153258Z">
        <seg>Ye Li chuckled. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶漓和她关系好，但凡哥哥们给她一个冷脸，她都要帮她打抱不平。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T140202Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T140202Z">
        <seg>Ye Li was close to her and whenever her brothers shot her a hostile look, Ye Li would stand up for her.  </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶漓嘴角冷冷勾起：“相信你的眼光？但凡你的眼光有司机叔叔一半的好，我也不至于丑到了现在。”她斜斜的扫了叶眉一眼。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T155155Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T155155Z">
        <seg>Ye Li smirked coldly and gibed, "Trust your taste? If your taste is half as good as the chauffeur's, I wouldn't have been so ugly." She gave Ye Mei the side-eye. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶漓在他们的印象中，那就跟贞子没两样。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T183906Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T183906Z">
        <seg>In their opinion, Ye Li was no different from Sadako from the horror flick. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶漓对叶眉的好，大家都看在眼里。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T155705Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T155705Z">
        <seg>Ye Li's kindness to Ye Mei was obvious to everyone.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶漓微微惊讶。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T191330Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T191330Z">
        <seg>Ye Li was slightly surprised. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶漓心中无比悔恨和愧疚。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T164553Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T164553Z">
        <seg>Ye Li's heart was filled with regret and guilt.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶漓心里一阵翻腾，她从床头翻出，输入了自己曾想拨出去却又不敢动手的电话号码。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T144919Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T144919Z">
        <seg>Ye Li's heart was in turmoil and she fumbled around the bed for her mobile phone. She then dialed the mobile number that she had once wanted to call but dared not do so.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶漓想到了自己自杀一事。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T165554Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T165554Z">
        <seg>Ye Li thought about her suicide.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶漓愣怔了一会，突然反应过来，不对，哥哥们看起来怎么好像是年轻了好多岁？</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T155217Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T155217Z">
        <seg>After being stunned for a while, Ye Li suddenly recovered from the shock and thought, 'Something is wrong. Why do my brothers all look so much younger?'</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶漓抬了抬下巴，又看了镜中露出了圆润的大脸，却五官精致的女孩一眼，突然勾了勾唇角。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T170940Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T170940Z">
        <seg>Ye Li lifted her chin, took a look at the girl in the mirror who had a large, round face but also exquisite features, and suddenly smirked.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶漓无视众人惊愕的目光，掏出了自己的书本，一副准备认真上课的模样。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T185005Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T185005Z">
        <seg>Ye Li ignored the looks of amazement from the crowd and took out her books, looking like she was ready to pay attention in class. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶漓点了点头：“三哥哥，不信你可以去问他，在你面前他不会那样，但是私底下对我的态度有多恶劣你不会知道，一瞬间，我感觉什么尊严都没了。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T140653Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T140559Z">
        <seg>Ye Li nodded and said, "Third Brother, if you don't believe me, you can ask him. He may not behave that way in front of you but you'll never know how hostile he is to me in private. I suddenly felt that I lost all my pride and dignity." </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶漓狠狠的掐了自己大腿一下，剧烈的刺痛却让她莫名的欣喜若狂。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T160148Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T155749Z">
        <seg>Ye Li pinched her thigh forcefully and the sharp, excruciating pain made her feel somewhat ecstatic and elated. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶漓的三哥叫做叶枫，这会儿还穿着帝都大学的校服，他染着一头蓝发，整个人看起来吊儿郎当的，可却是如今帝都大学的校草兼学霸，娱乐圈的当红一线大明星，全国女人心尖上的男神！可他依然还是一个妹控！</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T164410Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T164410Z">
        <seg>Ye Li's third brother was named Ye Feng. He was still wearing the uniform of Beijing University and he had a head full of blue hair. He seemed nonchalant and sloven but he was the most handsome boy in school and the star student of Beijing University. He was also a famous A-list celebrity in the showbiz industry, and the idol of all women in the nation! Yet, he was also particularly indulgent towards his younger sister! </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶漓的声音却蓦然一冷：“脸大就不能见人了？非要藏着掖着？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T152948Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T152701Z">
        <seg>Ye Li retorted with a sudden hostility in her tone, "What's wrong with having a large face? Must I hide it?"</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶漓的心一疼。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T160620Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T160620Z">
        <seg>Ye Li's heart ached. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶漓的性格虽然不好，经常得罪人，但是大多时候都是恼羞成怒的生气，什么时候这么会说话了？</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T140911Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T140911Z">
        <seg>Although Ye Li did not have a good temper and often offended others, it was mostly because she was infuriated after feeling ashamed. Since when had she ever been so sharp-tongued? </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶漓的母亲是名门之后，叫做秦歌，父亲是大世家的少爷，叫叶明，两人青梅竹马，门当户对，几乎是所有人都艳羡的存在。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T182226Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T182226Z">
        <seg>Ye Li's mother, Qin Ge, was from a wealthy and famous family while her father, Ye Ming, was the Young Master of a major family. The two of them were childhood sweethearts, and their families were a perfect match. They were a couple who left almost everyone green with envy. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶漓的瞳孔中染上意一丝血色。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T133408Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T133404Z">
        <seg>There was a tinge of blood in Ye Li's eyes. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶漓的耳朵一瞬间有些发麻。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T145123Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T145123Z">
        <seg>Ye Li's ears turned a little numb all of a sudden. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶漓看向三位有几分相似却同样帅气俊美的哥哥。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T163321Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T163321Z">
        <seg>Ye Li looked at her three brothers who somewhat resembled each other but were equally handsome and suave. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶漓眼眶通红的看着三人关心的脸色，眨了眨眼睛，将泪意压了下去，“哥，我真没骗你们，我也不为难，之前我是因为于向阳一直没有拒绝我，所以以为他也对我有意思，才会一直追求他，可前几天情人节我找他的时候，他已经拒绝我了，还，还说我恶心，我又不是没有尊严的人，人家既然都拒绝我了，我也不可能纠缠不休，没了他，我嫁谁不是嫁？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T140149Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T140122Z">
        <seg>Looking at their concerned faces, Yu Xiangyang blinked and held her tears back."Brothers, I'm really not lying to you guys. I'm not feeling conflicted either. Previously, I thought that Yu Xiangyang liked me too because he did not reject me. That's why I kept pursuing him. However, when I looked for him on Valentine's Day a few days ago, he rejected me and said that I'm disgusting. Well, I have some dignity too. Since he has already rejected me, I can't possibly cling onto him and pester him continuously. Without him, I can still marry someone else." </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶漓睁开的眼睛，就对上了三张帅气到令人尖叫的俊脸。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T154032Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T153918Z">
        <seg>As soon as Ye Li opened her eyes, she was greeted with three handsome and swoon-worthy faces. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶漓知道是自家三哥哥是因为昨天的事情去找于向阳麻烦了。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T160137Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T160137Z">
        <seg>Ye Li knew that her third brother had gone to argue with Xiangyang because of what happened yesterday. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶漓笑了笑，感动的说：“等他们回来了，我一定好好说说他们，要是再这样对你，我就生气了。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T141319Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T141319Z">
        <seg>Ye Li smile and said as if she was touched, "When they come home, I'll definitely criticize them. If they treat you like that again, I'll really get angry." </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶漓笑着往后慵懒一靠，语气轻飘飘的，“哎呀，跟你开个玩笑而已，瞧把你吓得，不知道的别人还以为我欺负你了呢，司机叔叔您说是不是？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T155427Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T155427Z">
        <seg>Ye Li smiled and leaned backwards while saying in a nonchalant tone, "Ah, I was just joking. Look how scared you are. Those who do not know might think that I bullied you. Uncle, don't you agree?"</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶漓翻出一把剪刀，将自己厚重的头发修理了一下，感觉差不多之后，才扎起高高的马尾。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T165440Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T165312Z">
        <seg>Ye Li whipped out a pair of scissors and gave her thick, heavy hair a trim. After being somewhat satisfied, she tied her hair back into a a high ponytail.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶漓自然是高兴接受。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T142646Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T142626Z">
        <seg>Ye Li naturally accepted her arrangements happily. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶漓起身。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201215T153838Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201215T153838Z">
        <seg>Ye Li stood up as she was told. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶漓这一次自杀醒来过来，好像是变了很多。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T160223Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T160219Z">
        <seg>Ye Li seemed to have changed a lot after regaining consciousness from her suicide attempt.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶漓这话分明就是在骂她！</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T140447Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T140447Z">
        <seg>Ye Li was obviously chastising her! </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶漓邪恶的想。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T171232Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T171232Z">
        <seg>Ye Li thought to herself evilly.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶漓都有些不敢相信，为什么徐凤年那样优秀的男人，会愿意娶这样一无是处的自己，还..还睡得下去...</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T143727Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T143727Z">
        <seg>Ye Li could not believe why a brilliant man like Xu Fengnian would marry such a useless woman like her. He could even... he could even bring himself to get intimate with her... </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶眉一脸委屈的说，那模样好似哥哥们又欺负她了一般。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T175906Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T175906Z">
        <seg>Ye Mei was speaking aggrievedly, as if her brothers had bullied her again. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶眉之前为什么会一直提醒叶漓要将脸遮住，不是没有原因的。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T182604Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T182604Z">
        <seg>There was a reason that Ye Mei repeatedly reminded Ye Li to hide her face previously. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶眉什么时候受到过众人的质疑，一张俏脸气的都红了。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T165316Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T165316Z">
        <seg>Since when had Ye Mei ever been doubted by the public? She was so enraged that her delicate face turned red. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶眉低着头，乖巧应是。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T151410Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T151410Z">
        <seg>Ye Mei lowered her head and assented obediently. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶眉出生的时候，叶枫年纪还小，知道的事情没那么多，对叶眉虽然不是很喜欢，但是也不会去多想。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T155313Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T155313Z">
        <seg>When Ye Mei was born, Ye Feng was still young and didn't know that much. Hence, he wouldn't think much about it even though he did not like her much. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶眉又是一愣，看向叶漓的眼中多了几分疑惑。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T152043Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T152043Z">
        <seg>Once again, Ye Mei was stunned and she looked at Ye Li with bewilderment in her gaze. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶眉听闻这话，指甲陷入了肉中。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T155758Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T155758Z">
        <seg>Upon hearing her words, Ye Mei clenched her fists, her fingernails digging into her flesh. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶眉和于向阳的计划，她势必要一步步的摧毁，让他们尝尝失去一切的滋味！</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T173914Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T173914Z">
        <seg>She would definitely destroy Ye Mei and Yu Xiangyang's plans, step by step, and make them get a taste of losing everything! </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶眉啊叶眉，我回来了！</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T133412Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T133410Z">
        <seg>'Ye Mei, Ye Mei, I'm back!'</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶眉噎住。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T150831Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T150831Z">
        <seg>Ye Mei choked. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶眉噎住了。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T170234Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T170234Z">
        <seg>Ye Mei choked. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶眉回过神，赶忙摇头，勉强笑笑：“我不是这个意思，姐姐你别误会，我没关系的。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T142134Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T142134Z">
        <seg>Ye Mei recovered from the shock and hurriedly nodded. Forcing herself to smile, she explained, "That's not what I meant. Sister, don't be mistaken. I'm perfectly fine." </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶眉她是很熟的，班上最优秀的女孩子。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T181034Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T181034Z">
        <seg>She was very familiar with Ye Mei, the most outstanding girl in class. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶眉委委屈屈的，一副被人冤枉的模样：“我真没有，我是你的妹妹，难道你还不相信吗？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T170136Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T170136Z">
        <seg>Looking as if she had been wronged, Ye Mei defended herself, "I really didn't. I'm your younger sister, do you still do not believe me?"</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶眉将收好的论文交了上去。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201215T153334Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201215T153334Z">
        <seg>Ye Mei handed in the papers that she had collected. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶眉心中疑惑。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T160136Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T160136Z">
        <seg>Ye Mei was filled with bewilderment. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶眉心里暗骂司机多管闲事，嘴上却无奈的说：“司机伯伯这你就不懂我们年轻人的时尚了。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T153423Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T153423Z">
        <seg>Ye Mei cursed the chauffeur for being too nosy in her head but nonetheless, she said helplessly, "Uncle, you don't understand the fashion trends of young people." </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶眉心里留了个心思，很想知道几人到底说了些什么。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T154356Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T154356Z">
        <seg>Ye Mei had a desire to find out what they talked about. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶眉愣了一下，随后笑着点头道：“放心吧，三哥哥，学校那边有我们，我已经跟老师说过了，你们不用担心。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T151109Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T151109Z">
        <seg>After being stunned for a while, Ye Mei nodded with a smile and said, "Rest assured, Brothers, we'll handle the matters at school. I've already informed the teachers. You don't have to worry."</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶眉捏了捏拳头，假笑了两声：“可能是眼光不同吧，我还是喜欢以前的发型，难道姐姐你还不相信我的眼光吗？”她一脸无奈的看向叶漓说。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T153611Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T153611Z">
        <seg>Ye Mei clenched her fists and laughed pretentiously. "Maybe, we just have different tastes. I still prefer her old hairstyle. Sister, don't you trust my taste?" she asked, looking at Ye Li helplessly. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶眉摇了摇头：“没关系的，这点委屈不算是什么，我也不想因为我的事情，让哥哥们总是生气。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T141642Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T141526Z">
        <seg>Ye Mei shook her head and said, "It's alright, this grievance is nothing. I don't want Brothers to be angry all the time because of me." </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶眉是班长，也是班级的团宠，无论是老师或者是学生，都十分的喜欢她。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T182247Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T182247Z">
        <seg>Ye Mei was the class president and the class' favorite. Both the teacher and her classmates adored her. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶眉是聪明人，知道怎样做对自己最有利。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T151657Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T151657Z">
        <seg>Ye Mei was a smart person who knew what would be best for her. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶眉气的脸都歪了。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T180742Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T180742Z">
        <seg>Ye Mei grimaced in exasperation. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶眉没想到她会突然生气，脸色微变，随后赶忙解释：“姐我不是这个意思，我只是觉得那样才好看，不过你要是非要这样也没关系呀。”她语气和善，听起来都是为她着想。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T153136Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T153136Z">
        <seg>Ye Mei didn't expect her to get angry all of a sudden. Her expression changed slightly and she hurriedly explained, "Sister, that's not what I meant.  I just think that you look better that way. However, it doesn't matter if you insist on having his hairstyle," she said in an amicable tone, sounding as if she was just sparing a thought for Ye Li. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶眉的脸一僵。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T163958Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T163958Z">
        <seg>Ye Mei's face stiffened.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶眉看着叶漓今天的装扮，眸光闪了闪，点了点头：“是呀，你也知道哥哥们不喜欢我。”她一脸黯然。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T141219Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T141209Z">
        <seg>Ye Mei looked at Ye Li's outfit today and her eyes glistened. She nodded and said, "Yeah, you know very well too that Brothers dislike me." Her expression was gloomy. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶眉眸光闪了闪，正欲说什么，就见叶洛三兄弟从楼上一脸阴沉的走下。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T145913Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T145910Z">
        <seg>Ye Mei's eyes glistened and she was just about to say something when she saw Ye Luo and her two brothers making their way downstairs with gloomy and sullen expressions.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶眉脸上的笑容徒然一僵，随后她反应过来，脸色发白，瑟瑟缩缩的说：“姐姐，你说什么，我怎么听不懂？你是不是误会了什么？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T155308Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T155308Z">
        <seg>The smile on Ye Mei's face suddenly stiffened, after which she recovered from the shock and turned pale. Shivering, she asked, "Sister, what are you saying? I don't understand. Are you mistaken about something?" </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶眉脸色一白，一副摇摇欲坠的姿态，表情好似受到了天大的委屈：“姐，姐姐，你怎么能这么想我，毕竟当时你去找向阳学长告白的事情是事实，我不想因为这件事而让你被大家所讨厌，才会让你道歉的，我都是为了你着想，你这样说，也太让我寒心了。”她说罢，红着眼眶低下了头，仿佛在多说一句，就忍不住要哭了一般，看的周围的男同学们是一阵怜惜，连带着看向叶漓的目光都带着敌意，仿佛她做了什么天理难容的事情。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T145529Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T145529Z">
        <seg>Ye Mei turned pale and seemed to be on the verge of collapsing. Looking extremely aggrieved, she said, "Sister, how could you think of me that way? After all, it's true that you had gone to confess to Senior Xiangyang. I want you to apologize because I don't want you to be hated by others. I am doing this all for your own good. Yet,you said that about me. I'm really disappointed." After saying that, her eyes turned red as if she was about to burst into tears if Ye Li went on. The boys around her were all showing her sympathy and looking at Ye Li with extreme animosity, as if she had committed a terrible sin.  </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶眉解释说：“姐，你道了歉，这件事就这样过去了，你若是不道歉的话，以后要被网络暴力的，你又不是不知道向阳学长的粉丝团队有多大，全校一半的女孩子都是他的粉丝，你就道歉吧！这样才能息事宁人啊。”叶眉苦口婆心的说。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T143223Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T143223Z">
        <seg>Ye Mei explained, "Sister, this matter will be over once you apologize, but if you don't, you will be cyber-bullied. It's not like you don't know how big Senior Xiangyang's fan club is. Half the girls in school are his fans. Just apologize to him! Only then can we settle this matter," Ye Mei said concernedly. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶眉这么聪明，不应该不知道这些才是。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T165935Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T165935Z">
        <seg>Since Ye Mei was that intelligent, she should have known this. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶眉那边不知道她有没有向别的人透露过，总之这会儿都不能打草惊蛇，要等他好好的揪出来，看看到底是谁想死！</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T155607Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T155607Z">
        <seg>They did not know if Ye Mei had told anyone else about the secret but in any case, they could not startle the culprit at this moment. They had to lure the culprit out slowly and see who wanted to die! </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>叶眉长相清纯，在这个年代，已是十分少有，还有人说她和当下最红拥有着玉女之称的女明星周莹莹十分相似，然后就被同学们封了个小玉女的称号，热度十分大，叶漓记得不错的话，这个时候，叶眉的微博粉丝都已经破百万了。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201210T134827Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201210T134827Z">
        <seg>Ye Mei looked rather pure and innocent. Girls like her were extremely rare in this day and age. Some even said that she resembled the female celebrity, Zhou Yingying, who was nicknamed 'Jade Girl'. She was extremely popular and if Ye Li remembered correctly, Ye Li probably had more than a million fans on Weibo now. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>司机也不是傻子，惊了一下，总感觉这大小姐好像是什么地方变了。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T155536Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T155536Z">
        <seg>The chauffeur was not a fool either. He got a shock as he felt that something about her had changed. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>吃了早餐两人一同上了车，叶眉终于忍不住问了起来：“阿漓，你的发型怎么变了，之前那个多好看啊，现在这样显得你的脸好大。”明明是关心的话，可听在当事人的耳中，却足够让人无地自容。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T151724Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T151724Z">
        <seg>After having breakfast, the two of them got inside the car where Ye Mei finally couldn't help but say, "Li, why did you change your hairstyle again? Your previous hairstyle was beautiful. Your current one makes your face look so large." Although she was clearly showing her some concern, her words were incredibly humiliating. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>同学们不禁没有怜悯半分，还幸灾乐祸，恨不得她死了最好，那样就没有人再缠着他们的偶像于向阳。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T163244Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T163244Z">
        <seg>The students did not show her any sympathy at all and they even gloated, wishing that she would just die. That way, no one would pester their idol, Yu Xiangyang. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>后来订婚一事不知道被谁传播了出去，大家都在说她一个大学生以前能过的那么好，肯定是被什么公司的老总包养。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T172152Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T172114Z">
        <seg>Later on, someone spread the word about her engagement and everyone said that she must have been a mistress of the CEO of a certain company in order to live in luxury as a college student. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>听说是因为出了什么意外，才和她父亲发生了亲密关系，然后怀上了和她一个年纪的叶眉，这事情发现的时候，秦柔已经大了肚子，想要打胎太伤身体，她妈妈不忍心，也就没再说什么，只是和丈夫的关系一度降到冰点，任由他如何补偿也不见起色，随着孩子长大，甚至一度抑郁，再加上秦柔若有若无的各种出现，整个人郁郁寡欢，生她的时候因为早产，大出血，没过多久便去世了。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T131007Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T130443Z">
        <seg>She heard that that woman had gotten intimate with her father because of a certain incident and later on, she got pregnant with Ye Mei, who was the same age as her. By the time they discovered that matter, Qin Rou's baby bump was already showing and it would getting an abortion when she was heavily pregnant would be harmful to her body. Her mother could not bear to let her get an abortion so she kept mum about it. However, the relationship between Ye Li's mother and father became extremely strained and regardless of how the latter coaxed her, she would not snap out of her gloomy mood. When giving birth to Ye Li, she went into premature labor and suffered an excessive loss of blood that caused her to pass away soon after labor. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>周围压抑的气氛在一瞬间好似消失的无影无踪。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T172713Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T172713Z">
        <seg>The somber and pressurizing ambiance around him seemed to disappear without a trace in an instant.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>周围的人也看了过去，“如果这件事真不关叶漓的事情的话，那她刚刚说的那些就太过分了。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T170816Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T170816Z">
        <seg>Everyone looked over too. "If this matter really has nothing to do with Ye Li, she has gone overboard with her words just now."</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>周围的人闻言，也是惊愕的看向叶眉。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T143917Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T143917Z">
        <seg>Everyone looked at Ye Mei in shock when they heard her words. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>周围的女生们一下就将目光移到了他的身上。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T185122Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T185122Z">
        <seg>The girls immediately shifted their gazes onto him.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>哥哥们都还没回来。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T172907Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T172907Z">
        <seg>Her brothers were not back yet.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>因为当初发生这些事情的时候，他们都还很小，所以并没有什么感觉，只有已经懂事的了大哥很是不喜欢这对母女，当初她竟然还埋怨他说他过分，现在想想，还真是愚蠢。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T132711Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T132711Z">
        <seg>When those things happened, they were still very young and hence, did not feel too emotionally affected. However, her eldest brother, who had already become conscious of the events around him, greatly disliked the pair of mother and daughter. Yet, she even resented him and criticized him for being overboard. After recalling those matters, she felt that she was really silly. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>因为联姻一事，她可谓是恨极了他们。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T163238Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T163238Z">
        <seg>She detested them to the core because of the arranged marriage that she had been forced into. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>因为这事是禁忌，叶家从没有人敢提。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T132019Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T132019Z">
        <seg>No one in the Ye Family dared to mention it because it was taboo. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>因为那个于向阳，和哥哥玩，根本就是不安好心！</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T141837Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T141837Z">
        <seg>Reason being Yu Xiangyang had ill intentions for being friends with her brother! </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>因此叶漓可没对叶眉少感激过，觉得她才是真正对自己好，关心自己的人。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T163048Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T163048Z">
        <seg>Hence, Ye Li was extremely grateful towards Ye Mei and she felt that the latter was the one who was truly concerned about her and genuinely treated her welll. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>因此，不少人挤破了脑袋都想进来。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T190345Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T190326Z">
        <seg>Hence, many people racked their brains and tried hard to get into the Faculty of Arts.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>因此，同徐凤年的关系再次降到冰点，甚至觉得，父亲和哥哥们出事，都是这个一手遮天的男人暗地所为，于是吵闹着要离婚。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T180142Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T180142Z">
        <seg>Hence, her relationship with Xu Fengnian became extremely strained again and she even felt that the invincible man, Xu Fengnian, was the one who caused her father and brothers to encounter that mishap. She thus kicked up a huge fuss and demanded a divorce. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>在学校，他能混的这么好，全靠自家三哥哥的帮忙。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T141859Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T141859Z">
        <seg>He managed to gain so much popularity in school, all thanks to her third brother! </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>在这个网络时代，不少人都借此为自己带来关注。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201210T133337Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201210T133337Z">
        <seg>In this digital age, many would use that to bring attention to themselves.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>外面的人谁提到文艺系的人，不都是女神女神的叫。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T184821Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T184821Z">
        <seg>Almost all girls in the Faculty of Arts would be deemed as goddesses to others.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>夜幕。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T152312Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T152312Z">
        <seg>It was nighttime. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>大家只知道她家很有钱，叶漓的生活很奢侈，但是没有人知道她就是那个第一世家的宝贝千金。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T172011Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T172011Z">
        <seg>Everyone only knew that Ye Li had a wealthy family and lived a luxurious life. However, no one knew that she was the precious daughter of the top family in the capital. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>大家看着久违的男神，这会儿都兴奋极了。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T190828Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T190828Z">
        <seg>Everyone was excited to see their idol whom they had not seen for a long time.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>大家虽然觉得奇怪，但是也没多想，毕竟两人从小一起长大。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T155740Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T155740Z">
        <seg>Although everyone found it peculiar, they did not think much of it.After all, the two of them had grown up together. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>大家都说她的眼睛像是狐狸精。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T170236Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T170236Z">
        <seg>Everyone said that her eyes were like that of a vixen. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>奇怪，按现在的情况，叶漓不应该是要死要活的闹吗？</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T151517Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T151517Z">
        <seg>'That's strange. Given the current situation, shouldn't Ye Li be throwing a huge tantrum and getting all hysterical?'</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>女佣顿时忐忑的说：“大小姐，每天的菜单都是厨房根据您的喜好准备的，我也不太清楚。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T144218Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T144218Z">
        <seg>The maid immediately said anxiously, "Missy, the dishes served everyday are prepared according to your preferences. I'm not very sure." </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>女同学却没注意，只是惊愕之余，一下就后悔了。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T175456Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T175456Z">
        <seg>However, the girl did not pay attention to it and simply felt stunned, after which she immediately regretted her actions. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>女同学本来都以为自己要完蛋了，没想到叶漓会突然这么说，她先是震惊，随后有些难以置信的看她：“你，你的意思是，不找我麻烦了？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T175330Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T175330Z">
        <seg>The female student originally thought that it was going to be over for her but to her surprise, Ye Li actually said those words. After being shocked, she looked at Ye Li in disbelief and asked, "You mean, you won't find trouble with me anymore?"</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>女孩子还是要软软糯糯的才好。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T183635Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T183635Z">
        <seg>It was better for girls to be soft and tender. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>女孩脖颈处白嫩嫩的肌肤吸引了他的注意，他趴在桌上，凑过脑袋喊了一声：“小胖回校了？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T191307Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T191307Z">
        <seg>The white and tender skin of her neck attracted his attention. Laying on the table, he inched closer and asked, "The little fatty has returned to school?"</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>女生一下就涨红了脸。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T140354Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T140354Z">
        <seg>The girl's face became flushed immediately. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>她不仅要回去，还要让努力变得优秀，将那些曾经欺辱过她的人，狠狠踩在脚下。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T163824Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T163824Z">
        <seg>Not only would she go back to school, she would also put in the effort to become an outstanding student, so as to climb above those who used to bully her. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>她不屑的瞥了撇嘴：“再说了，我之前对他也同大多粉丝一样，纯属爱慕，脑残追星，哪有什么深刻的感情，还没有那个值得我去为他死的影响力，懂？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T164732Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T164732Z">
        <seg>Pursing her lips disdainfully, she continued, "Besides, I only purely adored him previously, just like most of his retarded die-hard fans. My feelings for him aren't deep at all and he doesn't have enough influence for me to want to kill myself for him, understand?"</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>她不顾几个男人的担忧，急忙问：“哥，今天是什么几年几月？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T162204Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T162204Z">
        <seg>Ignoring the fact that they were worried, she anxiously asked, "Brother, what's the date today?" </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>她为了保持身材，每天吃的都很少，哪里像是叶漓一样，想吃什么就吃什么，不过她也乐得开心，自己在家虽然比不过叶漓，但是到了外面，呵呵。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T150942Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T150942Z">
        <seg>In order to stay in shape, Ye Mei ate very little food everyday, unlike Ye Li who would eat whatever she wanted to her heart's content. However, she was elated about that. Although she was inferior to Ye Li at home, things were different outside. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>她为什么要这么做呢？</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T160058Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T160051Z">
        <seg>'Why did she do that?'</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>她之前因为自杀一事，在家中休养了一个星期，根本就不知道这老师安排了论文要写。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201215T154413Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201215T154413Z">
        <seg>She had been recuperating at home for a week after she tried to commit suicide. She did not know that the teacher had tasked them to write a paper. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>她也才知道，原来自己的母亲，曾遭受了这么一遭。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T132156Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T132156Z">
        <seg>She also found out how much her mother had actually suffered back then.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>她二十三岁嫁给徐凤年，虽然前面恨得多，但是结了五年婚，之后意外怀孕之后也就收了心，同那个男人好好过日子。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T175257Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T175257Z">
        <seg>Although she was filled with hatred at the beginning of her marriage to Xu Fengnian when she was 23 years old, she stopped feeling that way after an accidental pregnancy. She decided to live on properly with him. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>她其实不丑，只是肥肉掩盖住了原本精致的五官，从这张脸上就可以看出，若是瘦下来，该是多么的漂亮。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T165120Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T165120Z">
        <seg>She was actually not ugly, but the fat on her face caused her exquisite features to be hidden. It was obvious that she would be gorgeous if she lost some weight. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>她几句话就将自己从刚刚误会中抽离，表示自己只是关心急切才会误会。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T165613Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T165613Z">
        <seg>She managed to get herself out of the misunderstanding just now in a few words, expressing her stand that she had only gotten the wrong idea because she was anxious and worried. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>她只得吞下这口气，委委屈屈的说：“对不起姐姐，我不是故意的，我看你那么喜欢学长，那天又跳了河，才会这样以为，你不要误会，我也是太担心你了。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T165538Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T165538Z">
        <seg>She had no choice but to bear with it and say aggrievedly, "I'm sorry, Sister, I didn't mean it. I just assumed so because I know how much you fancied Senior and you jumped into the river that way. Please don't get the wrong idea, I was just too worried about you."</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>她可不觉得曾经的自己，能吸引这个帅哥的注意。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T191420Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T191420Z">
        <seg>She did not think that the old her could attract the attention of the hunk. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>她吸了吸鼻子，有些委屈：“徐凤年？我是阿漓，你什么时候娶我回家？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T145215Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T145215Z">
        <seg>She sniffled and said, feeling a little aggrieved, "Xu Fengnian, I'm Li, when will you marry me?"</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>她在学校这么久，一向都是众人夸赞艳羡的存在。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T180846Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T180846Z">
        <seg>Throughout the years that she had been in school, everyone had always been envious of her and she would be showered with compliments all the time. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>她大学那会浑浑噩噩的，再加上已经过去了八年，说实话，大学这些人她没一个能叫上名字的。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T190928Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T190928Z">
        <seg>She was muddled up during college and eight years had passed since then. To be frank, she did not remember the names of any of her college schoolmates. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>她弯着月牙般的眼睛，笑意盈盈的开口，可那语气却莫名让人脊背发凉。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T155445Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T155445Z">
        <seg>Although she was grinning widely, her tone was somehow hair-raising. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>她强忍着上前给对方一巴掌的冲动，硬是扯出了一抹笑：“我没事。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T173656Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T173652Z">
        <seg>Resisting the urge to go forward and slap Ye Mei, Ye Li forced herself to put on an insincere smile and answered, "I'm fine." </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>她怕自己稍微大声一点，就会忍不住大哭出声。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T164814Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T164814Z">
        <seg>She was afraid that she would burst into tears uncontrollably if she were to speak any louder. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>她急忙整理了一下裙摆，起身上前，担忧的问：“大哥，我姐姐怎么样了，她醒了吗？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T150502Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T150502Z">
        <seg>She hurriedly adjusted the hem of her skirt, stood up, and walked forward. She asked worriedly, "Brother,how is Sister? Is she awake now?" </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>她怨怼的看了叶眉一眼，终究是低下了头：“对不起，我没想到事情原委并不如你妹妹所说，反而误会了自家的人，我也不知道如何才能挽救今天发生的事情，但是我是向阳粉丝团101群的队长，群里几千号的粉丝都听我的，要是哪一天你有什么事情需要帮忙，我一定尽所有能力帮你，对了，你想要进群吗？我可以给你当副团长。”她有些紧张的看向叶漓，生怕别人不买自己的单。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T175904Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T175904Z">
        <seg>After glancing at Ye Li timidly, she looked down in the end and said, "I'm sorry, I didn't expect the truth to be different from what your younger sister said. I ended up misunderstanding a fellow fan. I don't know how to make up for what happened today but I'm I'm the leader of the 101 Xiangyang Fanclub and the thousands of members all listen to me. If you ever need help, I'll definitely do my best to help you. By the way, do you want to join the club? I can make you the deputy leader," she said, looking at  Ye Li a little nervously, afraid that they would not believe her. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>她扯了扯嘴角，笑容却很冷，说出的话更是让人莫名：“之前喜欢不代表现在喜欢，人都是会变的，阿姨您说呢？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T145635Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T145635Z">
        <seg>She smirked coldly and her words were rather bewildering. "Just because I liked it in the past doesn't mean that I like it now. People are bound to change.Auntie, what do you think?"</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>她扯了扯嘴角，表情颇为不屑。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T140343Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T140343Z">
        <seg>She smirked with a look of disdain. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>她是这帝都第一世家的大小姐，本该是人上人的存在，又怎能再过那样的生活？</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T164442Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T164442Z">
        <seg>She was the heiress of the most powerful family in Beijing and she should have been a highly mighty existence who was superior to all. How could she live like that again?</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>她暗暗咬了咬牙，算了，在这个家里，谁对你都是唯命是从，不敢反驳，可到了学校，我看谁还会认同你半分？</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T160647Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T160647Z">
        <seg>She gritted her teeth secretly and thought, 'Forget it, everyone obeys you in this house and no one dares to go against you but once we get to school, let's see if anyone will agree with you.'</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>她有些不确定的目光落到了叶漓身上。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T181057Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T181057Z">
        <seg>She looked at Ye Li with some uncertainty. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>她本来就有些胖，再加上贪吃，就是早餐吃的也是叶眉的双倍，后来继母秦柔还特意请了个厨师给她做什么营养餐，说是这样既能补充营养，又不会变胖。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T142633Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T142622Z">
        <seg>She was a chubby glutton who used to eat twice of Ye Mei's portion for breakfast. Later on, her stepmother, Qin Rou, even specially hired a chef to prepare nutritious meals for her, claiming that it would give her a nutritional boost while keeping her weight in check. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>她清楚的记得，自己被叶眉关在那个私人医院的时候，已是2028年。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T162405Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T162405Z">
        <seg>She clearly remembered that it was the year 2028 when Ye Mei locked her up in that private hospital.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>她爸曾说，她的性格就和她的妈妈如出一辙，不善言语，不喜解释，宁愿自己受委屈也不会说上半分。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T163634Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T163634Z">
        <seg>Her father once said that her character was just like her mother's. She was not good with words, did not like to explain herself. She would rather be wronged than say anything more.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>她留着一头黑长直的头发，画着淡淡的素颜妆，给人一种清纯可人的感觉，相比较叶漓的圆润，她就十分的清瘦，风一吹就倒的柔弱女性，很能激起男人的保护欲，学校大半的男生都视她做女神。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T173426Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T173426Z">
        <seg>She had long and straight black-colored hair and wore some light makeup which gave her a touch of innocence. A stark contrast to the chubby Ye Li, she was extremely skinny and weak, as if she would be blown away easily by the wind. She would easily arouse the protective desires and nature of men. As a result, more than half of the male students in school saw her as their goddess. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>她的名声已近坏到了骨子里，所以无论怎么做，无论做什么，在别人的眼中都是恶意的。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T163315Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T163315Z">
        <seg>She had a terrible reputation and no matter what she did, they would still find her malicious. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>她的心脏狂跳了两下，这样熟悉的感觉，自己真的死了？</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T160050Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T160035Z">
        <seg>Her heart pounded vigorously twice. 'What a familiar feeling. Am I really dead?'</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>她的性格简直就被叶眉拿捏的死死的。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T141857Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T141857Z">
        <seg>Ye Mei had taken complete advantage of her character. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>她自小怕水，这会儿竟然能为了这事能做到这一步，三人心里又是恨自己不该这么逼她，又是气她为何这么冲动。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T155044Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T155044Z">
        <seg>Ever since she was a child, she had been afraid of water. Yet, she actually took things so far because of that matter. The three men blamed themselves for forcing her and were also angry at her for being so impulsive. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>她自然是欣喜至极，几乎是想也没想便答应了对方，之后听了对方的话以死相逼，成功拿到了离婚协议书。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T180538Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T180538Z">
        <seg>She was naturally overjoyed and she almost agreed to let him help her, without hesitation at all. Later on, she heeded his advice and successfully managed to get the divorce papers signed by threatening Xu Fengnian with her own life. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>她虽然也是叶家二小姐，但是和叶漓在叶家的地位却天差地别。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T151605Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T151605Z">
        <seg>Although she was also a daughter of the Ye Family, her status in the family was worlds apart from Ye Li.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>她要是多问，姑且还会让这三人反感。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T151640Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T151640Z">
        <seg>If she asked any more questions, they would be repulsed and annoyed by her. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>她觉得叶漓和叶眉是两姐妹，这事叶眉肯定是告诉了她，但是叶漓偷懒没写。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201215T154457Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201215T154457Z">
        <seg>She thought that Ye Mei must have informed Ye Li since they were sisters, and that Ye Li was just too lazy to write it. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>她说到这里，掀了掀眼皮子：“我也不能白受了这个委屈不是？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T171826Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T171826Z">
        <seg>At this point, she looked up and said, "I can't be wronged for nothing, right?"</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>她跳河一事是真，虽然也有因为表白被拒的因素在里面，但是更多的是因为要嫁给徐凤年和同学们的欺辱嘲笑。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T164321Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T164321Z">
        <seg>It was true that she had jumped into the river and although the rejection was part of the reason it was mostly because of the humiliation that she suffered for having to marry Xu Fengnian, and the mockery from her classmates. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>她身份太过敏感，所以一直是处于隐秘状态，除了叶眉和哥哥们，学校里的人几乎都不知道。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T171456Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T171456Z">
        <seg>Due to the sensitivity of her identity, she had always been keeping it a secret. Other than Ye Mei and her brothers, no one else in school knew about it. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>她这样找叶漓的茬，对方竟然不怪罪她。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T175509Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T175509Z">
        <seg>She made things hard for Ye Li but the latter did not blame her at all. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>她高中之前一直是十分优秀的学生，只是高考的时候因为睡过头，试卷只填了一半，勉强凑够分数进了帝都大学。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T160810Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T160810Z">
        <seg>Before she went to High School, she had always been an outstanding student but due to the fact that she had overslept on the day of the national college entrance examinations, she only had time to complete half of the exam script and barely made it through to Beijing University.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>好不容易熬到了生下孩子，于向阳突然出现，说要帮助她离开。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T180353Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T180353Z">
        <seg>After a great deal of hardship, she finally gave birth to her child and Yu Xiangyang suddenly appeared, claiming that he would help her leave. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>好想他！</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T144716Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T144716Z">
        <seg>'I miss him so much!'</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>如今的叶漓，刚满二十岁，就读帝都中心大学，是大二艺术系的学生。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T142504Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T142504Z">
        <seg>The current Ye Li had just turned twenty years old and was a Year Two college student at Beijing University. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>如今要是没了哥哥，她看他还如何星途辉煌！</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T141926Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T141923Z">
        <seg>'Let's see how he can achieve stardom and fame without Third Brother!'</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>完了完了，这个女的和叶眉从同一辆车上下来，那肯定也不是一般人。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T130336Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T130336Z">
        <seg>'Oh dear, it's over for us. This girl alighted from the same car as Ye Mei. She's definitely not an ordinary person.'</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>容是没整，被家里人拦住了。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T163521Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T163521Z">
        <seg>However, she did not end up going under the knife because she was stopped by her family. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>寂静的房间中，隐约听到了女人微弱的呼吸声。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T152334Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T152334Z">
        <seg>In the quiet room, the faint sounds of a woman breathing faintly could be heard. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>对了，若非三哥突然出事，那影帝之位恐是永远也轮不到他吧！</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T173743Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T173743Z">
        <seg>'Right, unless Third Brother suddenly encounters mishap, the title of the Best Actor will never, ever go to him!'</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>对于她这种重口味的人来说，她是最讨厌吃这些味道奇怪的营养餐的。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T145312Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T145312Z">
        <seg>Having always had a preference for flavorful food, she absolutely detested eating strange-tasting nutritious meals. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>对于自家小妹不愿意同徐家定亲还想不开自杀一事，三个男人都十分的愤怒。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T154642Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T154642Z">
        <seg>The three men were furious that their little sister had tried to take her own life because she was unwilling to accept her marriage with the Xu Family. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>对于这种不好好学习，一心只想着谈恋爱，名声又不好的学生，程艳是一点都不喜欢。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T181633Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T181633Z">
        <seg>Cheng Yan did not like students like her who had poor grades and reputation, and were only obsessed with falling in love.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>导师笑着回应了一声：“小眉啊，等会将论文收一下，上课交给我。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T182211Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T182211Z">
        <seg>The teacher answered smilingly, "Ye Mei, please collect the thesis papers later and hand them to me in class." </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>小胖好奇怪，今儿个给人的感觉全变了。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T191807Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T191807Z">
        <seg>'Little fatty seems so strange, she gives of a completely different vibe today.'</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>就听程艳不悦的问：“你的论文呢？怎么没交？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201215T153912Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201215T153912Z">
        <seg>Cheng Yan questioned in displeasure, "Where's your paper? Why didn't you submit it?" </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>就在这紧张忐忑且难熬的等待中，“叮咚”一声突然就在寂静的会议室中响起，接着，接二连三的声音陆续响了起来。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T172445Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T172354Z">
        <seg>In the midst of this nerve-wrecking and unbearable wait, a sudden 'Ding-dong' sounded in the conference room, followed by a series of other sounds. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>就是太相信你的眼光了，以至于我上辈子丑了半辈子。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T154945Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T154945Z">
        <seg>'I spent my previous life being ugly because I trusted your taste too much.'</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>就算是她道歉了又如何，道歉了，粉丝们就会买单吗？</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T165911Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T165911Z">
        <seg>Even if she apologized, so what? Would his fans buy it? </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>就算是搭不上关系，出去随口炫耀说自己和他们在一个系，那也要被外人羡慕死。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T190416Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T190332Z">
        <seg>Even if they could not get close to him, they could still go round showing off and saying that they were from the same faculty as him, so as to leave others green with envy. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>就连她叶漓，不也对叶眉好的不得了？</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T133132Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T133128Z">
        <seg>Even Ye Li had been very nice to Ye Mei. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>就连那个原本恼怒的粉丝听叶漓的话之后，也有些怀疑了起了事情的真实性，特别是叶眉自己也不敢肯定了的时候，她突然就觉得自己好像是真的误会了人家，刚刚还放话威胁别人，自己成了恶人。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T170528Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T170528Z">
        <seg>Even the fan who was originally infuriated with Ye Li, began to doubt the authenticity of the matter after hearing Ye Li's words, especially since Ye Li dared not confirm it too. At that moment, she suddenly felt that she had really misunderstood Ye Li and that she was a villain for threatening Ye Li just now. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>已经过了八年，很多事情她都记不清了。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T142428Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T142428Z">
        <seg>Eight years had passed, and she couldn't quite remember many of the events. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>帅气的人走到哪里都受欢迎，更别说这人还是他们学校男神榜排名第三的人。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T185226Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T185226Z">
        <seg>Handsome guys would definitely attract attention and be popular wherever they go, not to mention, he ranked in third place on the School Beau rankings. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>帝都中心繁星庄园。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T152306Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T152306Z">
        <seg>In Starry Manor in Beijing. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>帝都大学全国排No.1，里面有着世界各地的学生，美女帅哥如云，所以即使是叶眉这样已经十分漂亮的存在，顶多也就只能算是个系花而已。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T161029Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T161029Z">
        <seg>Beijing University was the top university in the country and its students came from all over the world, many of whom were extremely good-looking. Hence, even a gorgeous girl like Ye Mei could only be considered the school belle of her faculty. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>常年被头发遮挡的肌肤，在阳光的映照下，几乎白的透明，刘海下若隐若现的眉毛，下面是那双摄人心魄的灵动双眼，圆润的脸也挡不住的精致五官。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T181911Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T181911Z">
        <seg>Her skin, which used to be covered by her hair all the time, was almost translucently fair under the sunlight and her eyebrows were vaguely revealed beneath her bangs. Her soulful eyes were enchanting and the chubbiness of her face could not hide the beauty of her exquisite features. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>平时他们工作都很忙，大哥跟着父亲忙碌着庞大的公司，二哥是教授，经常会被邀请全国各地讲课。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T173000Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T173000Z">
        <seg>They were usually busy with work. Her eldest brother was busy with managing the huge company with their father while her second brother, who was a professor, was often invited to give lectures all over the country.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>平时光是吃营养餐，她都还要备用一堆零食才能吃饱，叶眉不信叶漓能够瘦下去，所以并没有将她的这番话放心上。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T151354Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T151354Z">
        <seg>Usually, Ye Li would have to eat a bunch of snacks after eating the nutritious meal in order to feel satiated. Ye Li did not believe that Ye Li could lose weight. Hence, she did not take her words to heart. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>平时叶漓最讨厌的就是自己的大脸，每次出门都恨不得用头发全部挡住，今儿个露出来了不说，竟然还觉得好看？</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T152450Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T152450Z">
        <seg>Ye Li's large face was what she usually hated the most and whenever she went out, she would be eager to cover her entire face with her hair. Yet, she revealed it today and even said that she looked great. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>平时因为名声差的原因，也没人跟她玩，这些男同学更不会去关注一个土里土气的丑八怪了。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T183949Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T183949Z">
        <seg>Usually, no one would hang out with Ye Li because of her bad reputation and the boys obviously wouldn't pay attention to a tacky and ugly girl. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>平时她不是跟自己关系最好了？</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T160130Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T160130Z">
        <seg>'Isn't she the chummiest with me?'</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>平时还有不少女的找上门，说是要打她。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T162921Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T162921Z">
        <seg>There would be plenty of girls looking for her and claiming that they wanted to hit her. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>平时都是被叶漓骂了，然后阴沉着一张脸离开，可这次脸色虽然也难看，但好像是因为其他什么事情。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T154343Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T154343Z">
        <seg>Usually, they would leave with sullen expressions after being berated by Ye Li. However, this time, they seemed to be sullen because of something else.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>当初叶眉上了女神榜的时候，很多人都去关注了她，自然而然会去观察她的生活，之后听说哈她还有个姐姐在同一个班级之后，大家都对叶漓产生了好奇，不少人慕名去找，结果没想到，竟然还是个又矮又胖，一眼看去只能看到头发女孩子。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T162312Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T162312Z">
        <seg>When Ye Mei was first listed on the goddess rankings, a lot of people started paying attention to her and her life. Later on, they found out that she had an older sister who was in the same class as her and thus, began to get curious about Ye Li. Many people tried to find out more about you but to their surprise, she was actually a short and chubby girl who had her face covered by her hair. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>当有一天，你所有引以为豪的都被人超过取代时，你又会是什么样的表情，肯定很精彩吧？</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T171225Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T171225Z">
        <seg>'It must be wonderful to see what you look like when everything you are proud of gets taken away from you by someone who surpasses you and replaces you, right?'</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>徐凤年：“.....”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T145224Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T145218Z">
        <seg>Xu Fengnian remained silent. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>徐晗愣了一下，拧着眉头看她。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T191747Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T191747Z">
        <seg>After being stunned for a while, Xu Han turned to look at her with a frown. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>徐晗猛不然就被她那双漂亮的眼睛勾了一下。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T191453Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T191453Z">
        <seg>Xu Han was attracted to the gaze in her pretty eyes. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>徐晗的脸逐渐冷了下去。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T191913Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T191913Z">
        <seg>Xu Han's face gradually turned cold and gloomy.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>心中虽然疑惑，但是叶眉没有多问。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T151536Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T151536Z">
        <seg>Despite being full of doubts, Ye Mei did not ask any more questions. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>心里本来就对她很不满，这会儿又不交论文，程艳说什么今儿个也得好好教训一下她。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201215T155226Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201215T155226Z">
        <seg>Cheng Yan was initially already extremely annoyed and displeased with her in the first place and to make matters worse, Ye Li failed to submit her paper this time. Cheng Yan was bent on teaching her a lesson no matter what. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>怎么变成了自己？</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T180805Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T180805Z">
        <seg>'Why did it suddenly become me?'</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>怎么这么安静。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T151521Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T151521Z">
        <seg>'Why is she so quiet?'</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>总之各种各样难听的话，让一向自命清高的叶漓几乎无地自容，再加上那一天，她匆忙找自己的男神于向阳解释的时候，被那个男人一脸厌恶的叫滚，这才绝望自杀。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T172614Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T172614Z">
        <seg>Bombarded by all sorts of insults, Ye Li, who had always been lofty, felt incredibly ashamed and to make matters worse, Yu Xiangyang, her idol,told her to get lost with a look of disgust when she hurriedly tried to give him an explanation. She was in so much despair that she tried to take her own life. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>恐是没想到这辈子还能听到叶漓这一声哥哥。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T165012Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T165012Z">
        <seg>They probably did not expect to hear Ye Li calling them her brothers again in their lifetime. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>想到自己当初的愚蠢，叶漓真恨不得给自己几个耳光。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T180609Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T180609Z">
        <seg>Thinking of her own stupidity, Ye Li really wanted to give herself a few tight slaps.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>想到这个可能，叶漓整个人都陷入了一阵震惊当中。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T162135Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T162135Z">
        <seg>At the thought of this possibility, Ye Li was flabbergasted. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>想到这个可能，女同学慌了。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T172812Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T172812Z">
        <seg>The girl panicked when she thought of this. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>想到这种可能，她又不禁有些慌了，暗暗埋怨起了叶眉，为什么自己都没有看见，就那样说，害的她还以为自己猜对了，才会那么理直气壮的找叶漓的麻烦。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T170650Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T170650Z">
        <seg>At the thought of this possibility, she couldn't help but be flustered and secretly blame Ye Mei. 'Why did Ye Mei say that even though she did not witness it with her own eyes? She caused me to think that I had guessed correctly and thus cause trouble for Ye Li self-righteously.'</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>想到这里，叶漓冷笑。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T173750Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T173750Z">
        <seg>Ye Li sneered at the thought of this. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>想到这里，叶眉暗暗冷笑，脸上却是一脸为难，“那也行，要是你能受得了的话。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T151256Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T151256Z">
        <seg>At the thought of this, Ye Mei secretly chuckled but she nonetheless put on a conflicted look. "Sure,if you can take it." </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>想着想着又想到那个男人了，叶漓的心里有些思念，她以为自己对徐凤年没有感情的，可当离开之后，日日夜夜脑袋里反复出现的人影却都是他，那时候她才知道，自己早已深陷无法自拔。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T144327Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T144327Z">
        <seg>As Ye Li thought about it, she was reminded of that man again, and missed him a little. She thought that she had no feelings for Xu Fengnian, but after she left, images of him kept popping up in her mind every day and night. Back then, she finally knew that she had already fallen for him and she couldn't help herself. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>戴着眼镜穿着白衬衫的看起来十分斯文的是叶漓的二哥，叶旬，二十四岁，帝都第一大学的老师，史上最年轻的天才教授,但这样一个优秀的男人，他也是个妹控。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T163838Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T163838Z">
        <seg>The scholarly-looking, bespectacled man who was wearing a white shirt, was Ye Li's second brother, Ye Xun, a twenty-four-year-old professor of Beijing University. He was the youngest ingenious professor in history. However, an outstanding man like him also doted on his younger sister greatly. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>所以一看叶漓这个眼神几个少年顿时就怂了，这会儿想要收了手机，却已然来不及。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T130008Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T130008Z">
        <seg>Hence, the few young men immediately became timid after seeing the look in Ye Li's eyes. It was too late for them to put their mobile phones away.  </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>所以也就是这样的性格，她和妈妈一样，都落到了那样不善而终的下场！</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T163659Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T163659Z">
        <seg>Hence, just like her mother whose personality was similar to hers, she ended up in a terrible situation! </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>所以影响不多，也没怎么多去注意过这个女生，只是道听途说关于她的黑料倒是不少。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T181433Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T181433Z">
        <seg>Hence, Ye Li did not have much of an influence and Cheng Yan never paid much attention to her. She had only heard that there was a lot of controversy about her. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>所以程艳硬是看了半天，才回过神来。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T182057Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T182057Z">
        <seg>Hence, Cheng Yan stared at her for a long time before reacting. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>所以说，自己重生回到了八年前？</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T162512Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T162512Z">
        <seg>'Does this mean that I've been reborn in the year 2020?'</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>所以谁都不知道，叶漓那厚重刘海下，隐藏着的到底是一张怎样的脸。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T184007Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T184007Z">
        <seg>Hence, no one knew that under Ye Li's thick bangs, laid a beautiful face. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>所以这也是叶漓为什么要留着厚重刘海的原因。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T170247Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T170247Z">
        <seg>That was also the reason Ye Li decided to have thick bangs. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>抬眼可见，遍地豪车。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T163911Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T163911Z">
        <seg>There were luxury cars everywhere.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>按照平时的情况，如今这会儿被骂的人不应该是叶漓才对吗？</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T180757Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T180757Z">
        <seg>Usually, Ye Li would be the one getting rebuked by everyone. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>按照平时，这丫头看到他们，不应该是大吵大闹的叫滚？</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T163220Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T163220Z">
        <seg>Ye Li would usually throw a huge tantrum and tell them to get lost whenever she saw them.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>换做上辈子的叶漓听这话，估摸着赶紧就把头发给拉下来了。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T151903Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T151903Z">
        <seg>If Ye Li were to hear those words in her previous life, she would have quickly pulled her hair down.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>新人新书求关照</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T165343Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T165343Z">
        <seg></seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>无论是颜值性格还是身材，她都排不上号。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T161339Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T161339Z">
        <seg>She was not qualified to be on the ranks, be it in terms of looks or figure. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>明明之前还不过是一个普通的不能再普通的女孩子，可现在只是换了个发型，给人的感觉就不一样了</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T181740Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T181740Z">
        <seg>Previously, she was just an extremely ordinary plain Jane but she gave off a drastically different vibe after changing her hairstyle. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>明明只要稍微放软一点态度，哥哥们都恨不得将全世界献到你的面前，你为什么还要那样寒他们的心。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T135128Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T135128Z">
        <seg>'As long as you soften your attitude, your brothers would clearly give you anything you want. Why did you have to disappoint them that way?'</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>明明叶漓刚刚那话就是在骂她眼光差，说她连个中年男人都不如，偏偏又用这种开玩笑的语气，司机还以为真是玩笑，可叶眉却感觉，叶漓就是故意的。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T160044Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T160044Z">
        <seg>Ye Li was clearly criticizing her for her poor taste just now and even said that her taste was worse than that of a middle-aged man. Yet, she made it sound light-hearted and even the chauffeur thought it was a joke. However, Ye Mei felt that she had done it on purpose. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>是了， 以往叶眉和叶漓关系最好，即使在叶漓被外面的人骂成那般，她也毅然站在自家姐姐身边，这样的作为可没少被人夸赞情深意切。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T144131Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T144117Z">
        <seg>Yeah, in the best, Ye Li and Ye Mei were the closest to each other and even when Ye Li was criticized by others, she would still stand on her sister's side. Hence, her behavior won her many praises for being loyal to her sister. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>是啊，叶漓不承认这件事是她的错的话，大家也不会怎么多想，毕竟没有人知道她到底是不是因为于向阳自杀，所以也不会多在意这件事。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T165817Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T165813Z">
        <seg>Yeah, if Ye Li did not admit that it was her fault, everyone else wouldn't think that way either. After all, no one knew if she had really tried to kill herself because of Yu Xiangyang. Hence, they wouldn't bother too much about that matter. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>是那么的熟悉，她一下就惊在了原地。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T154241Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T154241Z">
        <seg>Their faces were so familiar that she immediately froze on the spot. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>更别说之前两人还是出了名的好兄弟。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T160007Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T160007Z">
        <seg>Moreover, the two were known to be best buddies in the past. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>更别说好好说句话。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T140806Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T140806Z">
        <seg>She obviously wouldn't speak to them nicely. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>更被说还是叶漓这种爱面子的人。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T191714Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T191714Z">
        <seg>Besides, Ye Li was a prideful person. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>最前面坐着的男人，正拿着文件看着，另一只指节分明的手指有节奏的在桌上有一下没一下的敲击，每一声仿佛都敲在了众公司高层的心上，众人秉着呼吸，大气也不敢喘上半分。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T172314Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T172306Z">
        <seg>The man seated right in front was reading a document in his hand while tapping his other hand, which had well-defined knuckles, against the table rhythmically every now and then. Every knock seemed to be landing on the hearts of the various senior executives of the company. Everyone in the room was holding their breaths, and no one dared not breathe loudly at all. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>有人惊呼出声。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T185149Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T185149Z">
        <seg>Someone exclaimed in surprise.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>有人擦了擦冷汗。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T130708Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T130708Z">
        <seg>Some of them wiped away their cold sweat. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>有人突然惊讶的猜测。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T131859Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T131859Z">
        <seg>Someone suddenly guessed in surprise. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>有人这么一说，其他人顿时反应了过啦。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T132312Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T132312Z">
        <seg>As soon as someone said that, everyons suddenly realized something. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>有什么事情不能好好说吗？</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T155102Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T155102Z">
        <seg>They felt that she could have talked things out with them properly. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>有时候十天半个月也不会来，有时候一来就是一个月。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T190813Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T190813Z">
        <seg>Sometimes he wouldn't come for 10 days or half a month, sometimes, he would attend school consistently for a month. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>本来只是听说没有得到实证的众人一听这话，对叶漓更是鄙夷。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T134159Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T134159Z">
        <seg>Those people who had only heard those rumors based on hearsay and did not have concrete evidence, were filled with disdain towards Ye Li after hearing those words. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>本来的等着她发火的叶眉一下就愣住了。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T142002Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T142002Z">
        <seg>Ye Mei, who was initially waiting for her to lose her temper, was stunned.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>本来还议论纷纷的众人听叶漓这话，也是一下禁了声，纷纷倒退了几步，生怕自己会被殃及。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T172850Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T172850Z">
        <seg>Those who were initially still discussing immediately fell silent after hearing Ye Li's words and they took a few steps back one after another, for fear that they would be implicated. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>来来往往的同学们，吵闹纷纷。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T163921Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T163921Z">
        <seg>The students coming and going were noisy and boisterous.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>果然！</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T162324Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T162324Z">
        <seg>Just as she expected! </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>桌上的叶眉也穿着同样的校服。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T173250Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T173250Z">
        <seg>Seated by the table, Ye Mei was also dressed in the same school uniform.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>楼下，叶眉母女正安静的坐在沙发上。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T145759Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T145759Z">
        <seg>Ye Mei and her mother were seated quietly on the couch downstairs. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>欺负自家妹妹的竟然不止是外人。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T140719Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T140719Z">
        <seg>It turned out that outsiders were not the only ones who were bullying their younger sister. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>正在几人偷偷议论之时，就见那女孩从兜里掏出了一颗棒棒糖含在口中，随后她突然抬眸，眼尾上挑，突然就看向了他们的方向。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T125116Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T125116Z">
        <seg>While the few of them were secretly discussing amongst themselves, Ye Li took out a lollipop from her pocket and put it in her mouth. She then suddenly looked up and looked in their direction, lifting the corners of her eye. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>正当几人准备好跑路的时候，突见那女生只是扫了他们一眼，蹙了蹙眉，便收回了目光，随后背着书包进了学校。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T130439Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T130439Z">
        <seg>Just as the few of them were getting ready to flee, they suddenly Ye Li frowning and looking away after just taking a glance at them. She then carried her bag and left the school. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>此时气氛正十分压抑。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T172049Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T172049Z">
        <seg> </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>毕竟之前那个长时间低着头走路的女孩，和如今这昂首挺胸，叼着根棒棒糖，一脸放荡不羁的女孩子相比，实在是一个天地的差距。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T132249Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T132152Z">
        <seg>After all, she used to walk with her head hung low. Yet, she was now walking with her head held high, a lollipop in her mouth, and a nonchalant expression. She was really worlds apart as compared to before. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>毕竟叶眉乖巧可人的形象已经深入人心，没有谁可能怀疑她。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T155342Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T155317Z">
        <seg>After all, Ye Mei's obedient and adorable image had been been deeply etched in their minds and no one would suspect her. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>毕竟这个时候，于向阳还是他的好兄弟。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T141406Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T141354Z">
        <seg>After all, at this juncture, Yu Xiangyang was still his close friend. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>没想到这小胖刘海下面，竟然藏着这么一双漂亮的眼睛。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T191509Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T191509Z">
        <seg>He did not expect there to be such a beautiful pair of eyes hiding beneath her bangs. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>没有那个女的愿意被一个男的这么称呼。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T191702Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T191702Z">
        <seg>No girl would want to be called so by someone of the opposite gender. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>灯光打在床上的人儿上，只见她双眼紧闭，满头大汗，仿佛正在经历什么难以言喻的痛苦。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T152734Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T152734Z">
        <seg>The light was cast on the person who was lying on the bed with her eyes closed, sweating profusely like she was experiencing some inexplicable agony. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>爸爸和哥哥他们绝对不会出事。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T173850Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T173850Z">
        <seg>She would ensure that nothing terrible would happen to her father and brothers. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>特别是她那双眼睛，微微扫过任何一人，都会让人有种被电击中的感觉。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T182800Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T182800Z">
        <seg>Her eyes in particular, would make everyone feel like they had been struck by an electric shock whenever she looked at them. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>现在叶眉故意这么说，就是暗示她哥哥们不想让她和她玩，然后自己势必又会去怪罪他们。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T140509Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T140509Z">
        <seg>Now that Ye Mei had deliberately said those words, she was clearly implying that her brothers did not want to let her look for Ye Li, and assuming that Ye Li would definitely blame them again. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>现在想想，自己不是也走上了同样的道路吗？</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T132213Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T132213Z">
        <seg>After thinking about it, she realized that she had also gone on the same path. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>现在想想，自己可真是蠢得过分。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T145526Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T145526Z">
        <seg>Now that she thought about it, she felt that she was really overly stupid.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>甚至对她这个继妹的好超过了她那几位亲哥哥。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T155711Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T155711Z">
        <seg>She even treated her stepsister better than her own brothers.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>甚至无法将丑这个字用在她的身上。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T184907Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T184907Z">
        <seg>In fact, she could not even be described as ugly. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>男人带着几分低沉的声音响起。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T145027Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T145027Z">
        <seg>The man said in a low voice. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>男人的夸赞，可没有女人口中的那么多弯弯道道。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T152012Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T152012Z">
        <seg>Compliments from men were much more straightforward than that from women. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>直到后面知道了真相，知道他是无辜的之后，才明白自己的作为有多么的可恨。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T144706Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T144655Z">
        <seg>She only found out the truth later and after discovering that he was innocent, she understood how detestable her actions were. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>相比较她的愤怒，周围的人更多的是震惊。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T140545Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T140534Z">
        <seg>While she was angry, the people around her were shocked.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>看到叶漓的瞬间她先是愣了一下，随后一脸惊喜的站了起来：“阿漓姐你醒了，还有哪里不舒服的吗？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T173503Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T173503Z">
        <seg>The moment she saw Ye Li, she was slightly stunned, after which she stood up with a look of surprise. "Sis Li, you're awake. Do you feel any discomfort?"</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>看吧叶漓，你上辈子是多么的愚蠢。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T134937Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T134937Z">
        <seg>'Look Ye Li, you were so silly in your previous life.'</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>看吧，那个男人都说好看。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T152000Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T151946Z">
        <seg>'See, even that man says it looks great.'</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>看多了骨干美女的男同学们，这会儿口水都快流出来了。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T183557Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T183557Z">
        <seg>The boys who were tired of seeing skinny beauties, were almost drooling at this moment.  </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>看来这两姐妹的关系，好似也并不是表面那么好啊？</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T170003Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T170003Z">
        <seg>'It seems that the relationship between these two sisters is not as good as it seems, huh?'</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>看看这关心的表情，要不是已经经历过一辈子，叶漓估摸要感动。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T173550Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T173550Z">
        <seg>If Ye Li hadn't had the experience of her previous life, she would have probably been touched by how concerned Ye Mei appeared to be. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>看着虽然微胖，却白白嫩嫩，朝气蓬勃的女孩，大家根本就没反应过来这是叶漓。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T182726Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T182726Z">
        <seg>Although she was slightly chubby, she was fair, tender, and bubbly. It took them a long while to realize that she was Ye Li. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>看着镜中圆润的自己，她微微叹了口气。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T164606Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T164606Z">
        <seg>Looking at her chubby self in the mirror, she sighed a little. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>看着镜中焕然一新的女孩子，叶漓掏出了手机，寻了个显瘦的姿势拍了几张，翻出了某人的手机号发了过去，并配文：“新发型好看吗？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T171846Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T171846Z">
        <seg>Looking at herself in the mirror after giving herself a makeover, Ye Li took out her mobile phone and took a few photos of herself in a pose that made her look thinner. She then sent it to someone's mobile number with a text that read, "How's my new hairstyle?"</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>看起来最为关心柔软的话，带来的后果却是致命。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T140528Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T140528Z">
        <seg>The consequences of her gentle words of concern were fatal. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>真是太傻了。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T170334Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T170334Z">
        <seg>She was really too silly. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>硬生生的去了几分美，还有些怪异。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T170203Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T170203Z">
        <seg>It made her look strange and less beautiful. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>秦柔心中一惊，总感觉刚刚叶漓露出的笑容很是恐怖，让她心中发凉，可再次看去时，却发现她的表情如常，刚刚那抹笑好似从未在她脸上露出一般。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T145735Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T145651Z">
        <seg>Qin Rou was astonished and she felt that Ye Li's smile was extremely terrifying. It even made her feel a cold chill in her heart. However, when she looked again, she found that Ye Li's expression was as per normal and it was as if that smirk never appeared on her face just now. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>程艳看了一会，就阴沉着脸道：“叶漓，你站起来。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201215T153832Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201215T153832Z">
        <seg>Cheng Yan looked at it for a while before saying with a sullen expression, "Ye Li, stand up." </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>穿着一身西装的是大哥叶洛，不过二十六岁，如今却已近叶氏集团的副总裁，下一任的叶家继承人。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T163459Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T163459Z">
        <seg>Her eldest brother, Ye Luo, who was wearing a suit, had already become the Deputy CEO of the Ye Corporation even though he was only twenty-six years old. He was the next successor of the Ye Family. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>突然，其中一人惊呼一声：“快看那不是咱们学校女神排名前五的叶眉吗？天哪，真的跟照片一样漂亮哎，快点拍，这可是难得的机会。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201210T134155Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201210T134155Z">
        <seg>All of a sudden, one of them exclaimed, "Look, isn't that Ye Mei, one of the top five in the goddess rankings in our school? Oh my god, she's really as beautiful as she looks in photos. Hurry and take a photo of her. This is a rare opportunity."</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>第二天，一条八卦新闻上了热搜。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T155627Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T155627Z">
        <seg>On the second day, the gossipy news made it to the hot search. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>等人走了，才有些风中凌乱的收回目光：“妈耶，刚刚那一瞬间我以为我要完了。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T130651Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T130651Z">
        <seg>After she left, some of them looked away in a flustered manner and said, "Damn it, I thought that it was going to be the end of us just now." </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>简直就像是换了个人。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T184107Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T184107Z">
        <seg>She was just like a completely different person. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>结果一秒，两秒，三秒过去。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T172532Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T172532Z">
        <seg>In the end, three seconds passed. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>结果大一期末考试的时候考了全班第一，就被怀疑作弊，老师也不相信她，好巧不巧的是，当时不知道谁往她的桌下丢了纸条，这一幕正好落到了监控中，叶漓弯腰捡笔的动作就成了她抄袭的实证。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T162452Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T162452Z">
        <seg>In the end, she managed to top her class during the final exams in her first semester of college, and got suspected for cheating. The teacher refused to believe her and coincidentally, someone tossed a piece of paper under her table, which was captured by the surveillance cameras. Ye Li's action of bending over to grab her pen became the evidence of her cheating. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>翻出自己的校服穿上，他们的校服偏海军风，下面是百褶裙，十分好看。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T171719Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T171719Z">
        <seg>She took out her school uniform, which had a navy style design and consisted of a pleated skirt. It was beautiful. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>而且叶漓说的也对，要不是刚刚叶眉笃定了她做了那样的事情，自己也不会一时冲动的威胁她，犯下了这样的大错！</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T175613Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T175613Z">
        <seg>Besides, Ye Li was right. If it wasn't for the fact that Ye Mei was certain that Ye Li had done that, she wouldn't have gone to threaten Ye Li impulsively and made such a huge mistake!</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>而且距离叶漓没来学校，不过一个多星期而已，但是这清冷的气质，这浑身散发的自信光芒，怎么看也不像是那个叶漓啊？</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T184057Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T184057Z">
        <seg>Besides, Ye Li had only been absent for school for a week, and the aloof aura and confidence did not seem like something Ye Li would have.  </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>而且，她正巧和阿漓一个班....</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T181716Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T181716Z">
        <seg>Besides, she was coincidentally in the same class as Ye Li... </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>而叶漓这个姐姐，排名9999+前都没有她的踪迹。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T161202Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T161202Z">
        <seg>On the other hand, her elder sister, Ye Li, was far from even the 9999th place. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>而叶眉的母亲，同样也是叶漓母亲同父异母的妹妹，甚至可以说，就是一小三的女儿，叫做秦柔。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T182334Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T182334Z">
        <seg>On the other hand, Ye Mei's mother, was likewise the half-sister of Ye Li's mother. In fact, she was the daughter of a mistress, and her name was Qin Rou. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>而她叶漓，叶家大小姐，二十岁之前，一直是上天的宠儿。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T161345Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T161345Z">
        <seg>On the other hand, Ye Li, the heiress of the Ye Family, was truly Heaven's favorite before she turned twenty. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>而此时楼下，坐着吃饭的只有叶眉母女。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T172901Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T172901Z">
        <seg>At this moment, Ye Mei and her mother were the only ones who were having a meal downstairs. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>腿上的疼痛不似作假，哥哥们的担忧又是那般清晰可见。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T162100Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T162100Z">
        <seg>The pain in her legs felt real and her brothers were clearly worried about her too. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>自己二十三岁就嫁给了徐凤年，之后就再也没有回过家了。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T155613Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T155613Z">
        <seg>She had married Xu Fengnian at the age of twenty-three and ever since then, she had never returned home. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>自己的低调和忍让，反倒是让那些人变本加厉。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T163655Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T163655Z">
        <seg>Her decision to tolerate and keep a low profile actually made those people go overboard. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>至于叶漓这个不良少女，一开始的惊愕过后，老师是看也不想多看一眼。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T182338Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T182338Z">
        <seg>On the other hand, the teacher stopped looking at Ye Li, the wayward girl, after being astonished for a while. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>若不是之后叶眉得逞之后，将所有一切同她炫耀，她恐是这辈子也无法知道真相。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T164645Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T164645Z">
        <seg>Had Ye Mei not shown off everything to her after getting her way, she would have never known the truth in her lifetime. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>虽然不得不承认，这样的她确实像是换了一个人一般。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T152513Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T152509Z">
        <seg>Although she undeniably looked like a whole different person, that was not what Ye Mei wanted to see. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>虽然两兄弟关系不错，但是叶漓很清楚，没有谁能在她三个哥哥的眼中比得过她，所以闹崩是迟早的事情。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T160211Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T160211Z">
        <seg>Although the two of them were good friends, Ye Li knew clearly that no one could compare to her, in the eyes of her brothers. Hence, it was only a matter of time before they fell out with each other. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>虽然从小家里人过度宠溺，但是叶漓的性格并没有变得娇蛮。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T163613Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T163613Z">
        <seg>Although she had always been overly pampered by her family, Ye Li did not become a spoiled and demanding brat. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>虽然他们这样拍照能获得一定的关注和资金，但是不是谁都想要红的，有些人就十分讨厌被人偷拍，听说前几天有个男的就是拍了个学校的风云人物被人当场抓包，结果第二天就被那人的粉丝们揍进了医院。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T125515Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T125515Z">
        <seg>Although they could get a certain number of followers and money from taking such photos, not everyone wanted to be famous. Some people hated having their photographs sneakily taken. A few days ago, one of the famous campus figures immediately caught someone taking photos of him red-handed. In the end, that person was beaten up by the famous figure and sent to the hospital.  </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>虽然叶漓的改变确实让人惊讶。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T133446Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T133403Z">
        <seg>Although they were indeed astonished by Ye Li's changes, that could not erase the scandals that she had been involved in previously. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>虽然在大学的生活过的是一点也不好。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T163734Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T163731Z">
        <seg>Although her life in college was simply a torture for her, she wouldn't drop out just because of that.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>虽然她觉得是同父异母，但是因为从小一起长大，叶漓跟她又同龄，所以她对叶眉并没有什么恨意，反倒是真心的将她当好姐妹对待。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T140419Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T140419Z">
        <seg>Although she felt that they were half-sisters, she did not have any hatred for Ye Mei and even genuinely treated her as her close sister because they grew up together and they were the same age. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>虽然是文艺系的系草，但是此人性格极差，没有人能和他搭上关系，或者说上几句话，不少表白的女孩子还听说被他直男直语气哭过。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T190005Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T185956Z">
        <seg>Although he was a beau of the Faculty of The Arts, he had a terrible personality and no one could get close to him or even speak to him at all. Rumor had it that many girls who confessed to him even cried because of his harsh and blunt words.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>虽然瘦确实穿衣好看，但是摸起来手感不好啊。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T183623Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T183623Z">
        <seg>Although thinner girls really tend to look better in clothes, they were not nice to touch. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>虽然胖，但是也不是没有好处的。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T165224Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T165224Z">
        <seg>Although she was chubby, there were benefits to that. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>要说于向阳，也是帝都大学风云人物之一。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T172635Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T172635Z">
        <seg>Yu Xiangyang was one of the influential figures in Beijing University. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>要说叶家这关系，也是比较复杂。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T182030Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T182030Z">
        <seg>Actually the relationships between the members of the Ye Family were rather complicated. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>要说叶家，如今也是帝都第一世家，同徐家在这座昌荣繁华的城市并列第一的两大超级世家。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T161314Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T161314Z">
        <seg>The Ye Family was now the top family in Beijing, alongside the Xu Family, the two being the most powerful families in this prosperous and bustling city. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>要说现在的叶漓，性格还是十分叛逆。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T160421Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T160421Z">
        <seg>Her current character was still very rebellious. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>见人散了开，艺术系的导师程艳才注意到了两姐妹。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T181015Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T181015Z">
        <seg>The arts tutor Cheng Yan, finally noticed the pair of sisters after everyone left. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>见她一副死猪不怕开水烫的表情，那女生恼怒至极，“那你就给我等着吧！”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T142617Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T142617Z">
        <seg>Seeing how stubborn and smug she was, the girl flew into a rage and barked, "Just you wait and see!" </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>见她竟然要闹到警察局，女同学的脸都白了。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T171837Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T171837Z">
        <seg>Seeing that she was actually going to the police station, the female student's face turned pale. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>记得不错的话，叶眉是系花吧。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T171013Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T171013Z">
        <seg>'If I remember correctly, Ye Mei is the school belle.'</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>说不定严重还会被学校退学，毕竟进过警察局的人都是有案底的，不管是学校，还是未来工作，都会有影响！</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T172757Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T172757Z">
        <seg>She might even get expelled by the school. After all, those who were detained in the police station would leave a record that would affect one both in school, and in the workforce!</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>说话的女生一噎，竟是被她怼的哑口无言。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T141613Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T141613Z">
        <seg>The girl who was speaking choked, falling speechless because of her insult. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>谁也看不清楚她此时脸上的狠色。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T181627Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T181621Z">
        <seg>None of them could see clearly the look of ruthlessness on her face. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>谁可知，迎接她的，竟是地狱...</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T180558Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T180558Z">
        <seg>Who would have thought that what greeted her was hell...</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>谁料之后爸爸和哥哥飞机失事，之后叶家无主，一度陷入了危机当中，之后叶眉跑来告诉她，说徐凤年为了叶家的家产，暗地里在收购叶家的公司，想要夺取叶家财产。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T175753Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T175753Z">
        <seg>To her surprise, after her father and brothers died in a plane crash, there was no one to take charge of the Ye Family and they slipped into a crisis. Later on, Ye Mei went to tell her that Xu Fengnian was secretly acquiring the Ye Family's company in a bid to encroach on the Ye Family's assets. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>谁知道她不仅没有瘦，还越来越胖了。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T143035Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T143035Z">
        <seg>However, not only did she not lose any weight, she even got chubbier. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>谁知道这位好姐妹，表面盛世白莲，背地里竟然是那般蛇蝎黑心。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T133326Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T133129Z">
        <seg>Who knew? Her wonderful sister looked kind and pure on the surface but beneath that facade, she was actually malicious and vicious. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>豪车划过繁华的街道，很快就停在了巍然屹立的帝都大学门口。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T163855Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T163826Z">
        <seg>The luxurious car cut through the bustling street and soon came to a halt in front of the majestic Beijing University.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>走过来的这个少年确实很帅，就是叶漓这种家中坐拥几个极品帅哥哥哥的人看了也不由的惊艳。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T191006Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T191006Z">
        <seg>The young man who walked over was indeed very handsome, and even Ye Li couldn't help but be impressed despite having three extremely handsome and dashing brothers at home.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>身下舒适的感觉告诉她，这一切都是真的，她真的重生了。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T142411Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T142411Z">
        <seg>The feeling of discomfort in her lower body told her that everything was real and that she had really been reborn.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>车子划过繁华的大街，很快就来到了帝都中心的贵族大学。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T160917Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T160917Z">
        <seg>The car drove past the bustling avenue and they soon arrived in the university for upper-class students in the center of Beijing. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>过了一个晚上，脑袋里面絮乱的记忆已经被她整理清楚。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T160357Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T160357Z">
        <seg>After an entire night, she had already sorted out all the messy memories in her mind. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>这三兄弟更是从未将她当妹妹来看。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T151623Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T151623Z">
        <seg>The three brothers had never treated her as their younger sister. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>这个位置，可是让她的身份地位在帝都大学十分崇高呢。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T171043Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T171043Z">
        <seg>That status of hers allowed her to be put on a pedestal and admired by everyone in Beijing University. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>这个出名还是因为叶眉的关系。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T161355Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T161355Z">
        <seg> </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>这个年代的人都十分会打扮了，偏偏叶漓进入学校这么久，竟然也没丝毫改变。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T162459Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T162459Z">
        <seg>In this day and age, most people were fashionable and dressed well. Yet, there was no change in Ye Li's appearance even though she had been admitted to the university for a long time. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>这个年纪就已经能装的这么深沉，不怪家里人的人都被她们两母女的表面所欺骗。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T173630Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T173630Z">
        <seg>At such a tender age, she was actually already able to put on such a convincing pretense. It was no wonder that the people in her family were deceived by the facades of Ye Mei and her mother. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>这个房间她从小睡到大，记忆深刻，但是在自家被叶眉那个无耻女人剥夺之后，这个房间就已经从此消失，如今又怎么会出现。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T160017Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T155747Z">
        <seg>The room, which she had slept in since she was a child, was deeply etched in her memory. However, it disappeared after the shameless woman Ye Mei appeared and snatched away her family. Since then, this room disappeared as well. Why did it appear again today? </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>这个时候的自己，还是一名大二的学生。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T160410Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T160410Z">
        <seg>At this point in time, she was still a Year Two college student. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>这个时候，程艳走进来了。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201215T152949Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201215T152949Z">
        <seg>At this moment, Cheng Yan entered. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>这么好的条件，她竟然当做丑陋而遮挡。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T170327Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T170327Z">
        <seg>She actually treated her beautiful feature as a hideous flaw that she wanted to hide. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>这些事叶漓二十岁之前都是不知道的。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T131525Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T131525Z">
        <seg>Ye Li did not know about those matters before she turned twenty. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>这些事情太过丢人，她不敢跟家里人说。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T163543Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T163543Z">
        <seg>Those matters were too embarrassing and she dared not tell her family about it.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>这件事叶漓记得很清楚。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T162022Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T162022Z">
        <seg>Ye Li remembered that incident very clearly.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>这件事闹的不小，全班人对她的态度都变了，老师也十分的厌恶她，叶漓被冤枉之后，都懵了，任由她如何解释也没人相信，还认为她知错不改，老师十分生气，罚了她打扫了一个月的卫生。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T162914Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T162914Z">
        <seg>That matter blew up and all her classmates' attitude towards her changed. Even her teachers were disgusted and resentful towards her. After Ye Li was wrongly accused, she was dumbfounded. No matter how she tried to explain herself, no one believed her. They even felt that she wasn't repentant. The teacher was extremely infuriated and punished her by making her do cleaning chores for a month.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>这会儿却被人传播了出去，害的小妹受到这样的对待。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T181441Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T181415Z">
        <seg>This time, it was leaked and caused their younger sister to be subjected to such terrible treatment. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>这会儿又有一穿着校服的少年走了进来。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T185022Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T185022Z">
        <seg>At this moment, another young man who was wearing a school uniform entered.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>这会儿好了吧，她知道委屈脱身，自己倒是成了笑话。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T170709Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T170709Z">
        <seg>'Great, now she gets to give herself an out aggrievedly while I've turned into a joke.'</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>这会儿对她说话的语气别提有多好了。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T182259Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T182259Z">
        <seg>At this moment, her tone was extremely pleasant. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>这会儿看向叶眉的目光，都有些怪异了起来。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T144613Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T144613Z">
        <seg>Everyone started looking at Ye Mei with peculiar gazes. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>这会儿自然是不可能交的出来的。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201215T154418Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201215T154418Z">
        <seg>Naturally, it was impossible to hand it in at this moment.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>这会儿还闹出了打架一事，更别说会有多忙了。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T173109Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T173109Z">
        <seg>Now that he had gotten involved in a fight, he would definitely be much busier. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>这会儿，就连叶枫也怒了：“他当真敢这么说？”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T140547Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T140532Z">
        <seg>This time, even Ye Feng was enraged. "He really had the audacity to say that?" </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>这会看到他这幅不在意形象竟然还如此帅气，不少女孩子都红了脸，有些甚至还拿出手机偷偷拍照。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T190143Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T190143Z">
        <seg>After seeing how handsome he was despite not caring about his appearance, many girls blushed and some even took out their mobile phones to secretly snap photos of him.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>这会脸色难看的紧。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T180904Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T180904Z">
        <seg>Her expression turned even more sullen. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>这叶漓真是可怜。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T170357Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T170357Z">
        <seg>'Ye Li is really pitiful.'</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>这叶眉也是，刚刚才帮着外人逼迫自家姐姐，这会儿竟然还要人家相信她，真是够让人无语的。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T170337Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T170337Z">
        <seg>'I really don't know what to say about Ye Mei. She was just helping outsiders to force their own sister, and now she wants everyone to believe her.'</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>这声音不大，只有两人听见。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T191324Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T191324Z">
        <seg>He was rather soft and only Ye Li could hear him. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>这是一个很残忍的选择， 但是叶漓不得不这么做。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T141819Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T141819Z">
        <seg>It was a cruel choice but Ye Li had no choice but to do so. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>这样漂亮的五官，但凡能瘦下来，那必定又是一娉娉玉立的美人。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T124715Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T124715Z">
        <seg>With such beautiful features, she would definitely be an elegant beauty once she lost weight. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>这样的人，就算是放在人群中，大家也不会多看一眼，甚至还觉得她那装扮辣眼睛。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T162358Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T162358Z">
        <seg>No one would take a second glance at her when she stood in a crowd and in fact, they might even find her to be an eyesore. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>这样的声音着实很难让人对她发火，不然就显得自己过于强势过分。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T144959Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T144959Z">
        <seg>Her voice made it difficult for others to get angry at her. Anyone who flared up at her would seem overly domineering and overboard. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>这次回校，她改头换面的样子，学校里的人都没认出自己。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T191346Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T191346Z">
        <seg>This time, no one in school could recognize her after her makeover. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>这简直就是要将她推入刀剑风口上啊。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T165921Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T165921Z">
        <seg>Ye Mei was simply pushing her to death. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>这话一出，不仅给对方台阶下不说，还变相的告诉大家，叶漓这是恼羞成怒了，才敢这么说话。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T141855Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T141642Z">
        <seg>Not only did she give the girl an out by saying that, she even indirectly told everyone that Ye Li said those words because she was ashamed and angry. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>这话一出，叶眉的表情微变，劝道：“这样不好吧阿漓，我吃的都太素了，你肯定受不了的。”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T150536Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T150536Z">
        <seg>As soon as she said those words, Ye Li's expression changed a little and she persuaded, "That doesn't seem appropriate, Li. My food is too bland, you definitely won't be able to stand it." </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>这话听起来好似真的为叶漓说话，可却变相的告诉大家，没错，你们猜对了，叶漓就是因为被人拒绝表白，才会跑去自杀！</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T134032Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T134032Z">
        <seg>Although she sounded as if she was really speaking for Ye Li, she was indirectly telling everyone that Ye Li had really tried to commit suicide because she had gotten rejected!</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>这话说出来，他势必会非常生气，甚至和于向阳断绝兄弟关系。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T141436Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T141436Z">
        <seg>If he were to say those things, Yu Xiangyang would definitely fly into a rage and sever their friendship.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>这辈子她不在做个怂包，不在因为那些冤枉和欺辱就抬不起头。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T163903Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T163903Z">
        <seg>In this life, she would no longer be a coward who would hang her head low just because she had been wronged and bullied. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>这辈子她再也不做一个与世无争的女孩，她要做一个魔女，哪怕人人唾之，也要将所有欺负过的自己的人狠狠踩在脚下！</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T171326Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T171326Z">
        <seg>In this life, she would never be a kind-hearted girl again! She would be a demoness who would trample on everyone who bullied her, even if she had to face the criticism of everyone!</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>这辈子她告诉自己，没关系，一切都可以重来，自己上辈子犯得错，这一世用一辈子来弥补，于是，她拨出了那熟悉的电话。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T145014Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T145014Z">
        <seg>In this life, she told herself that it didn't matter because she could start anew again and she could atone for all the mistakes that she had made in her previous life. Hence, she dialed the familiar phone number.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>这辈子，她需要换一个方式生活，一个谁也惹不起的方式！</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201209T163751Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201209T163751Z">
        <seg>In this lifetime, she had to change the way she lived and made sure that no one could provoke her! </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>进了教室，她又刷了一波惊奇的目光。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T182532Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T182532Z">
        <seg>Once she entered the class, she again attracted many gazes of amazement.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>那个人给她带来的改变，就这么夸张吗？</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201214T191901Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201214T191901Z">
        <seg>'Did that person bring about such a drastic change to her?'</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>那个男人一向沉默寡言，更别说好好解释，因此两人的好不容易缓和的关系再次破裂，叶漓更是拼了命的想要逃离帝家。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T180305Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T180305Z">
        <seg>His silence and lack of a proper explanation caused their relationship, which had gotten better after a great deal of painstaking efforts, to break down once again. Ye Li desperately wanted to leave the family. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>那人生，仿佛开挂了一般。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T121820Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T121820Z">
        <seg>It was as if her life had suddenly became better.</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>那副情深意切的模样不似作假。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T150553Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T150553Z">
        <seg>The look of concern and affection on Ye Mei's face seemed genuine. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>那同学见叶眉这样，心里稍微舒坦了一些，于是抬着下巴施舍一般的语气说：“行，那我就再给她一次机会，给我道歉，并主动站出来承担这件事的责任！”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T142801Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T142801Z">
        <seg>Seeing Ye Mei's reaction, the girl felt a little more at ease. Hence, she raised her chin and said condescendingly as if she was doing some charity, "Fine, in this case I will give her another chance to apologize to me, and take the initiative to come forward to take responsibility for this matter!"</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>那女生闻言，冷哼一声：“叶眉同学不是我不给你面子，你看你姐姐这丝毫没有悔悟之心就罢了，还在这里死不承认，真是没见过这种人，反正我话是撂在这里了，你一天不道歉，我们向阳粉一天不会放过你！”她放下狠话。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T142038Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T142038Z">
        <seg>Hearing her words, the girl humphed coldly and said, "Ye Mei, it's not that I don't want to spare her on your account but look how unrepentant your sister is. She even refuses to admit to her mistake. I've really never seen such a person before. Anyway, I'm only going to say this once. If you don't apologize, we, the fans of Xiangyang, will never let you off!" </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>那女生闻言，脸一下就黑了：“我是向阳的粉丝，我自然是他粉丝的名义维护他！”</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T140002Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T140002Z">
        <seg>Upon hearing her words, the girl's face turned sullen and she exclaimed, "I'm Xiangyang's fan. Of course I'm defending him as a fan!" </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>那时候上叶家依旧很庞大，整个帝都能动的了手的也就只有徐家。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T175905Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T175905Z">
        <seg>At that time, the Ye Family was still extremely powerful and the Xu Family was the only family in Beijing that could touch them. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>那是一个怎样的眼神啊，锋利如刀，似是一瞬间划破了空气，准确无误的刺中了他们。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201213T125136Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201213T125136Z">
        <seg>Her gaze was sharp like daggers which seemed to have cut through the air and stabbed them accurately. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>镜中的女儿脸很大，还留着厚重的齐刘海儿，土里土气不说，还显得头大。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T164719Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T164719Z">
        <seg>The girl in the mirror had a large face and thick and neat bangs which not only made her look like unsophisticated, it also made her head look large. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>除了有钱，好像是其他的都跟她没什么关系了。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T142904Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T142904Z">
        <seg>Apart from being wealthy, she did not have any other positive attributes. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>难..难不成自己重生了？</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T162110Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T162110Z">
        <seg>'Did... did I get reborn?' </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>难怪她会冲动的跑去自杀，难怪她会那样恨他们，原来学校里的那群人才是罪魁祸首！</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T181018Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T181018Z">
        <seg>It was no wonder that she had decided to kill herself in a moment of impulse. It turned out that her schoolmates were all culprits!</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>难道叶漓醒来，又闹了吗？</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201208T150423Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201208T150420Z">
        <seg>'Did Ye Li throw a tantrum again after regaining consciousness?'</seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
    <tu>
      <tuv lang="zh-CN">
        <seg>面对曾经疼爱自己的父亲和哥哥们的各种相逼，同学们的嘲笑，性格极端的她直接跳了学校的池塘，险些淹死。</seg>
      </tuv>
      <tuv lang="en-US" changeid="amandafong" changedate="20201206T162015Z" creationid="amandafong" creationdate="20201206T162015Z">
        <seg>Faced with all kinds of pressure from her father and brothers, who used to love and dote on her very much, as well as the mockery of her classmates, Ye Li, who had an extreme personality, jumped straight into the pond in school where she almost drowned. </seg>
      </tuv>
    </tu>
<!-- Alternative translations -->
  </body>
</tmx>
